<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>My Corner of the Internet</title>
  <subtitle></subtitle>
  <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/"/>
  
    <updated>2024-03-30T20:16:05Z</updated>
  
  <id>https://shanewrogers.lol</id>
  <author>
    <name>Shane Rogers</name>
    <email>swrogers@omg.lol</email>
  </author>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title></title>
      <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/Trying out GitJournal/"/>
      <updated>2024-03-16T04:19:31Z</updated>
      <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/Trying out GitJournal/</id>
      <content type="html">
          <![CDATA[
      <h1>Trying out GitJournal</h1>
<p>There is always this desire to want to be able to take quick notes, or jot something down while on the go. Perhaps blog something when nowhere near a laptop or keyboard.</p>
<p>Maybe this little application can be an answer?</p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title>One Step At A Time</title>
      <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/one-step-at-a-time/"/>
      <updated>2024-03-16T22:01:14Z</updated>
      <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/one-step-at-a-time/</id>
      <content type="html">
          <![CDATA[
      <h1>Things that still need to be done</h1>
<p>Not that this will ever actually be completed, but here are some things that I might want to consider doing.</p>
<ol>
<li>I need to get an emacs capture template made for new posts.</li>
<li>Maybe get an emacs capture template for normal pages.</li>
<li>Pull in stuff from my other sources:
<ul>
<li>Pixelfed</li>
<li>Targaryen House Mastodon</li>
<li>Raindrop.io</li>
<li>Last.fm / audioscrobbling</li>
<li>Currently reading</li>
<li>Finished reading</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Linkroll and stuff</li>
</ol>
<p>As much as I'm not a fan of emacs literate config, might this be a decent time to convert the ol' doom config over to a literate config and put it here? I dunno...</p>
<p>I believe the theme I'm using already has the Open Graph stuff, but I need to double check that.</p>
<p>I might want to look into the Echo Feed stuff.</p>
<p>I don't know if it would be possible to set up the indieweb login stuff, but maybe.</p>
<p>I do need to make sure that I always - <em>ALWAYS</em> - remember to <code>git pull</code> before pushing...seeing as how I'm also experimenting with blogging from the GitJournal app.</p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title>Another Step Down</title>
      <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-step-down/"/>
      <updated>2024-03-18T16:04:54Z</updated>
      <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-step-down/</id>
      <content type="html">
          <![CDATA[
      <h1>One more step down</h1>
<p>Now, we have at least one yasnippet for helping to make blog posts.</p>
<p>Maybe I can also sort out a way to wrangle org capture templates to create a markdown file with the frontmatter, then I won't even need the snippet.</p>
<p>Probably should come up with a better file name scheme, too...maybe something with a date on it.</p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title>Capture Template Done?</title>
      <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/capture-template-done/"/>
      <updated>2024-03-18T17:35:37Z</updated>
      <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/capture-template-done/</id>
      <content type="html">
          <![CDATA[
      <h1>Step Two, Maybe</h1>
<p>Capture template might be ready to go, now.</p>
<p>Created a new markdown post in the proper directory, with a prompt for the file name, then prepends the year-mm-dd to the file name. Opens a nice empty file, ready for the yasnippet.</p>
<p>I could probably put more into the capture template to do away with the snippet.</p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title>Now that we have reloaded</title>
      <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/now-that-we-have-reloaded/"/>
      <updated>2024-03-18T18:05:18Z</updated>
      <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/now-that-we-have-reloaded/</id>
      <content type="html">
          <![CDATA[
      <h1>Capture template - Sorta Done</h1>
<p>Well, it's done enough that I think I'm gonna call it <em>good enough</em> at this point. I'm not particularly happy with the yasnippet yet, in that I can'ts eem to get the <code>tags</code> entry items to space over and have to do that manually. Whatever. It's fine. It's all good.</p>
<p>I think I need to add a setting into the org capture portion to make sure that the capture window takes up the whole frame, or at least isn't mirrored in another portion of my frame. It's all good, though. That must be the Pete the Cat in me talking. Ha.</p>
<p>I also had to suppress the emacs warning from yasnippet that complained about changing the buffer - so I may have to either live with what I'll consider a hack, or come up with a better way to insert the ISO creation time stamp for the date frontmatter.</p>
<p>I'm sure there is more.</p>
<p>Still plenty of stuff to work on: setting up some data store files to pull in my other feeds, checking into basic webmentions (because I'm super, uber popular....ha)....among other items.</p>
<p>This slug is acting funny.</p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title>Yes, this is a possible slug-tacular title.</title>
      <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/yes-this-is-a-possible-slug-tacular-title/"/>
      <updated>2024-03-18T21:21:42Z</updated>
      <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/yes-this-is-a-possible-slug-tacular-title/</id>
      <content type="html">
          <![CDATA[
      <h1>Slugs and stuff</h1>
<p>That last post had an issue with the permalink and slug. I thought it might have been related to my simple super uber basic slug code....but then, doesn't eleventy create its own slug with the <code>permalink</code> entry in the frontmatter?</p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title>About ready to let things grow naturally now</title>
      <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/about-ready-to-let-things-grow-naturally-now/"/>
      <updated>2024-03-29T21:13:04Z</updated>
      <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/about-ready-to-let-things-grow-naturally-now/</id>
      <content type="html">
          <![CDATA[
      <h2>On how this site is gonna go</h2>
<p>Yeah, I think at this point I'm about at a spot where I think It's time to just let things grow naturally and have features (insofar as they can be called that...) added naturally. Or, organically, if one would rather refer to that type of growth as such.</p>
<p>I've got my org capture template setup in my doom emacs config that creates the file with a datestamp and a prompted file name. I've got my swrlol yasnippet that creates the frontmatter for me. It might be nice if I were to take that prompted value for the file name and use it for the title within the frontmatter - I might look into that one.</p>
<p>I've today added my short stuff slash notes category. I need to add an rss feed just for that - also perhaps give it the ability to take its own tags as well.</p>
<p>After that and a bit of time, it'll be ready to begin looking into getting things cross posted over to mastodon.</p>
<p>Then it'll be time to also look into pulling some posts from pixelfed. I'd still rather somebody else host images for me, since that is quite the expense and hassle that I would not like to enter into.</p>
<p>I am really enjoying eleventy, though. It's pretty nice.</p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
    
    <entry>
      <title>Another day, another day</title>
      <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-another-day/"/>
      <updated>2024-03-30T20:16:05Z</updated>
      <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-another-day/</id>
      <content type="html">
          <![CDATA[
      <h2>Another entry in the daily stuff</h2>
<p>Let's see what we can do about getting something written on the daily, eh? I don't know if I'll be successful here, but it's important to have some kind of goal I guess. I'll file these under the <a href="/tags/journal" title="journal tags">journal</a> tag (note to self: come back and make that a proper link to the journal tag page) so I can do whatever with them in the future.</p>
<p>Today it's Saturday. Really, most normal adults/kids/people/pigs/horses/spiders/lizards/whatever would probably love a good weekend day. For some reason, I'm not always a fan. I don't know why, I think it's because I miss working. Not that I'm a workaholic, but I find that I enjoy what I do in my normal life. There's just too much stuff that needs to be done during the weekend to maintain a house and home.</p>
<p>Not that I don't like that stuff, either. It's nearly lawn mowing season - I absolutely love mowing the lawn! I don't think that 12 year old me would believe that statement, but it's true. It's a time to put the buds in and listen to some nerdcore! (note to self: I should make a section dedicated to what I'm listening to, perhaps pull in my lastfm stuff as a data collection via rss.) It's also about time to make another attempt at getting some fruit trees planted, which is always fun.</p>
<p>Right now, I'm just sitting here, typing away, listening to the <em>Snoopy Show</em> on AppleTV. Outside, the weather is pretty nice, we've got the rather large bounce house set up outside for the youngest kiddo, it's kinda noisy too. It's funny, you know, the things that we purchase for our kids: the things that we would have killed to have when we were young. A swingset slash jungle gym. A bouncehouse. Various playground type equipment. Stuff that never gets used.</p>
<p>Well, I guess that's not completely true. It does get used, some. Just not as much as one would have hoped. Meh.</p>
<p>Sigh, well, I'm out of coffee. Of course, who needs coffee at three thirty in the afternoon? Stupid rhetorical question, that. I always need coffee.</p>
<h2>Setup stuff, emacs wise</h2>
<p>This particular emacs setup, what I'm writing in now, from an older laptop running current Pop_OS, isn't really to my liking. Even though it's running the same doom setup as my work machine, it's not perfect. My work machine, I guess I can't really say that I run emacs from that device since I ssh into a locally hosted kvm box via wsl....meh, there are differences. I wish I could grok <code>guix</code> or <code>nixos</code>, but alas, I'm stil stuck in the realm of linux.</p>
<p>Where was I? Oh yes, I do have <code>org-capture</code> templates set up that work just fine. I need to get the popup capture buffer to take the whole frame, though. I don't like that it also visits the capture buffer in the originally opened frame as well. It's an annoyance.</p>
<p>I'm sure there should be more. I think I'm going to wait until I've got more, eh, content, here before I get various rss feeds set up for feeding into some of my social sites. I feel that I should probably &quot;own my social&quot;, too, and I do have at least one I run - but it's certainly a chore. We shall see.</p>
<p>With that, I'm out.</p>

    ]]>
      </content>
    </entry>
  
</feed>
