<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>My Corner of the Internet Feed for 100DaysToOffload</title>
	<subtitle>Just my little corner of the internet.</subtitle>
	
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/"/>
	<updated>2024-06-18T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://shanewrogers.lol</id>
	<author>
		<name>Shane Rogers</name>
		<email>swrogers@omg.lol</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Not From the Peanut Gallery</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-from-the-peanut-gallery/"/>
		<updated>2024-06-18T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-from-the-peanut-gallery/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;I am notoriously difficult to purchase any kind of gift for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything that I generally want, I have a tendency to go ahead and make the purchase at any and every time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything that I &lt;em&gt;don&#39;t&lt;/em&gt; immediately buy, is most likely because the item just cost too much and I can not justify the purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do have a few things that I enjoy though, and high on that list is anything and everything Peanuts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Charles_M._Schulz&quot;&gt;Charles Schulz&lt;/a&gt; variety, of course. Charlie Brown, Snoopy, Woodstock, all of them! I&#39;ve been enamored of the crew since I was a child.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of my earliest memories of reading, not just making things up and babbling and looking at pictures, is of laying on the living room floor, the Sunday Comics spread open in front of me, reading and laughing at Peanuts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember Dad asking me if I was actually reading, then him being surprised when I said yep!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of that to say that my wife is pretty awesome! She always knows what to get me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.some.pics/swrogers/6671b4a30cb0e.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A Charlie Brown Squish Mellow. &quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best squishmellow of all time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 3/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The banana thing</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-banana-thing/"/>
		<updated>2024-06-17T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-banana-thing/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Last night my head was killing me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning my head was still killing me. I have to say that I consider myself extremely fortunate to have a very flexible career that affords me the ability to take time when I need it. It is not something that need be done very often - not for myself anyhow - but I&#39;m more than happy to take it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, I&#39;m sitting in the quiet of the dinning area, watching one of the kiddos make some kind of banana &lt;em&gt;slash&lt;/em&gt; chocolate &lt;em&gt;slash&lt;/em&gt; puff pastry dessert that he and Mom had seen online somewhere. It looks interesting, and I&#39;m sure it&#39;ll be tasty for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did I mention that this kiddo is only just out of fifth grade? He&#39;s been baking and cooking for what seems like a couple of years now. The kiddo is very driven and fairly well rounded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Normally, anyhow. Sometimes these kids will surprise with some of those &amp;quot;You asked what?!&amp;quot; questions. They are all super intelligent, have gifted IEPs in school, but still - on occasion - they show their age and remind us that they are still children, and need guidance to make their way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that is perfectly fine. It&#39;s what we are here for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 2/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Happy Fathers Day</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/happy-fathers-day/"/>
		<updated>2024-06-16T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/happy-fathers-day/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;As today prepares to come to an end, I&#39;m sitting here at home waiting on the ibuprofen and acetaminophen cocktail to do its thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We did make it to Worlds Of Fun, as a way to have a fun Father&#39;s Day. It was a pretty good day. There were a couple of us that managed to get in a few good coaster rides, facilitated by some decently short lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had never ridden the Prowler before today - definitely one of my new faves. It&#39;s an older wooden coaster, I think it&#39;s celebrating a birthday this year as well. I&#39;m kind of surprised that I had never been on it previously, but sure glad that I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I&#39;ve just got to get over the heat and sun induced ache that I&#39;ve put myself through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-sunday-linkdump&quot;&gt;The Sunday Linkdump &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#the-sunday-linkdump&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t really have a whole lot this week, as I&#39;ve just not really had the time to go down too many rabbit holes this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tiltedwindmillpress.com/product/ryoms-preorder/&quot;&gt;Michael W Lucas&#39; Run Your Own Mail server preorder&lt;/a&gt; I&#39;ve previously run my own mail server, sort of successfully, but not from scratch. This book is on my radar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.phrack.org/index.html&quot;&gt;Phrack Magazine&lt;/a&gt; Somebody had brought up 2600 magazine awhile ago, and this is another (non printed) magazine that&#39;s dedicated to the scene. I&#39;ve read 2600 for decades, and also enjoy reading this one when it&#39;s available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like I say, not a lot this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;end-stuff&quot;&gt;End stuff &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#end-stuff&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m going to consider this my first entry into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://100daystooffload.com/&quot;&gt;#100DaysToOffload&lt;/a&gt; challenge for the next 365 days. I don&#39;t have any special pages set up for these, besides using the hashtag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 1/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
