<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>My Corner of the Internet Feed for c25k</title>
	<subtitle>Just my little corner of the internet.</subtitle>
	
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/"/>
	<updated>2025-01-19T03:05:11+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://shanewrogers.lol</id>
	<author>
		<name>Shane Rogers</name>
		<email>swrogers@omg.lol</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>My couch to 5k start</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/my-couch-to-5k-start/"/>
		<updated>2024-09-27T14:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/my-couch-to-5k-start/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Yesterday I started my first session of the &lt;em&gt;Couch to 5K&lt;/em&gt; program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m not going to say that it was completely brutal, but it was definitely a challenge for myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve never been a runner. Nor a jogger. Heck I haven&#39;t even been much of a walker with the exception of the last year, maybe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But for some reason, I&#39;ve got this crazy idea that I would like to run a 5K.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slowly but surely I have been trying to work my body to to being prepped, in some way, for the coming activity. By walking and trying to keep a brisk pace, by going longer and longer distances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point, I can do right at a three mile walk in about 40 to 45 minutes. My average is just over a 13 minute mile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Certainly not an Olympic caliber, but I&#39;m okay with that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, using one of the many &lt;em&gt;C25k&lt;/em&gt; apps out there, was my first stress test. I would say that I succeeded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure, it was not easy, and yeah I was looking forward to that &amp;quot;You are on run 8 of 8&amp;quot; notification, but I survived.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did the complete 3K (I think) trek in 30 minutes, finishing very close to the end of our trail at the conclusion of the program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, silly me still wanted to finalize my &lt;em&gt;actual&lt;/em&gt; normal walk path, so I continued on for another less than mile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That, I admit and know now, was a mistake. According to my Fitbit app, the first two miles were under 13 minutes each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last was at an over 17 minutes pace. Yeah, no good, and I felt it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m looking forward to doing this again today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 42/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
