<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>My Corner of the Internet</title>
	<subtitle>Just my little corner of the internet.</subtitle>
	
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/"/>
	<updated>2024-05-24T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://shanewrogers.lol</id>
	<author>
		<name>Shane Rogers</name>
		<email>swrogers@omg.lol</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Capture Template Done?</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/capture-template-done/"/>
		<updated>2024-03-18T17:35:37+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/capture-template-done/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h1 id=&quot;step-two%2C-maybe&quot;&gt;Step Two, Maybe &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#step-two%2C-maybe&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capture template might be ready to go, now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created a new markdown post in the proper directory, with a prompt for the file name, then prepends the year-mm-dd to the file name. Opens a nice empty file, ready for the yasnippet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could probably put more into the capture template to do away with the snippet.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Now that we have reloaded</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/now-that-we-have-reloaded/"/>
		<updated>2024-03-18T18:05:18+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/now-that-we-have-reloaded/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h1 id=&quot;capture-template---sorta-done&quot;&gt;Capture template - Sorta Done &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#capture-template---sorta-done&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, it&#39;s done enough that I think I&#39;m gonna call it &lt;em&gt;good enough&lt;/em&gt; at this point. I&#39;m not particularly happy with the yasnippet yet, in that I can&#39;ts eem to get the &lt;code&gt;tags&lt;/code&gt; entry items to space over and have to do that manually. Whatever. It&#39;s fine. It&#39;s all good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I need to add a setting into the org capture portion to make sure that the capture window takes up the whole frame, or at least isn&#39;t mirrored in another portion of my frame. It&#39;s all good, though. That must be the Pete the Cat in me talking. Ha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also had to suppress the emacs warning from yasnippet that complained about changing the buffer - so I may have to either live with what I&#39;ll consider a hack, or come up with a better way to insert the ISO creation time stamp for the date frontmatter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m sure there is more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still plenty of stuff to work on: setting up some data store files to pull in my other feeds, checking into basic webmentions (because I&#39;m super, uber popular....ha)....among other items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This slug is acting funny.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Yes, this is a possible slug-tacular title.</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/yes-this-is-a-possible-slug-tacular-title./"/>
		<updated>2024-03-18T21:21:42+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/yes-this-is-a-possible-slug-tacular-title./</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h1 id=&quot;slugs-and-stuff&quot;&gt;Slugs and stuff &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#slugs-and-stuff&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That last post had an issue with the permalink and slug. I thought it might have been related to my simple super uber basic slug code....but then, doesn&#39;t eleventy create its own slug with the &lt;code&gt;permalink&lt;/code&gt; entry in the frontmatter?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>About ready to let things grow naturally now</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/about-ready-to-let-things-grow-naturally-now/"/>
		<updated>2024-03-29T21:13:04+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/about-ready-to-let-things-grow-naturally-now/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;on-how-this-site-is-gonna-go&quot;&gt;On how this site is gonna go &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#on-how-this-site-is-gonna-go&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I think at this point I&#39;m about at a spot where I think It&#39;s time to just let things grow naturally and have features (insofar as they can be called that...) added naturally. Or, organically, if one would rather refer to that type of growth as such.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve got my org capture template setup in my doom emacs config that creates the file with a datestamp and a prompted file name. I&#39;ve got my swrlol yasnippet that creates the frontmatter for me. It might be nice if I were to take that prompted value for the file name and use it for the title within the frontmatter - I might look into that one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve today added my short stuff slash notes category. I need to add an rss feed just for that - also perhaps give it the ability to take its own tags as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that and a bit of time, it&#39;ll be ready to begin looking into getting things cross posted over to mastodon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then it&#39;ll be time to also look into pulling some posts from pixelfed. I&#39;d still rather somebody else host images for me, since that is quite the expense and hassle that I would not like to enter into.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am really enjoying eleventy, though. It&#39;s pretty nice.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Another day, another day</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-another-day/"/>
		<updated>2024-03-30T20:16:05+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-another-day/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;another-entry-in-the-daily-stuff&quot;&gt;Another entry in the daily stuff &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#another-entry-in-the-daily-stuff&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s see what we can do about getting something written on the daily, eh? I don&#39;t know if I&#39;ll be successful here, but it&#39;s important to have some kind of goal I guess. I&#39;ll file these under the &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/journal&quot; title=&quot;journal tags&quot;&gt;journal&lt;/a&gt; tag (note to self: come back and make that a proper link to the journal tag page) so I can do whatever with them in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today it&#39;s Saturday. Really, most normal adults/kids/people/pigs/horses/spiders/lizards/whatever would probably love a good weekend day. For some reason, I&#39;m not always a fan. I don&#39;t know why, I think it&#39;s because I miss working. Not that I&#39;m a workaholic, but I find that I enjoy what I do in my normal life. There&#39;s just too much stuff that needs to be done during the weekend to maintain a house and home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not that I don&#39;t like that stuff, either. It&#39;s nearly lawn mowing season - I absolutely love mowing the lawn! I don&#39;t think that 12 year old me would believe that statement, but it&#39;s true. It&#39;s a time to put the buds in and listen to some nerdcore! (note to self: I should make a section dedicated to what I&#39;m listening to, perhaps pull in my lastfm stuff as a data collection via rss.) It&#39;s also about time to make another attempt at getting some fruit trees planted, which is always fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now, I&#39;m just sitting here, typing away, listening to the &lt;em&gt;Snoopy Show&lt;/em&gt; on AppleTV. Outside, the weather is pretty nice, we&#39;ve got the rather large bounce house set up outside for the youngest kiddo, it&#39;s kinda noisy too. It&#39;s funny, you know, the things that we purchase for our kids: the things that we would have killed to have when we were young. A swing set slash jungle gym. A bounce house. Various playground type equipment. Stuff that never gets used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I guess that&#39;s not completely true. It does get used, some. Just not as much as one would have hoped. Meh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sigh, well, I&#39;m out of coffee. Of course, who needs coffee at three thirty in the afternoon? Stupid rhetorical question, that. I always need coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;setup-stuff%2C-emacs-wise&quot;&gt;Setup stuff, emacs wise &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#setup-stuff%2C-emacs-wise&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This particular emacs setup, what I&#39;m writing in now, from an older laptop running current Pop_OS, isn&#39;t really to my liking. Even though it&#39;s running the same doom setup as my work machine, it&#39;s not perfect. My work machine, I guess I can&#39;t really say that I run emacs from that device since I ssh into a locally hosted kvm box via wsl....meh, there are differences. I wish I could grok &lt;code&gt;guix&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;nixos&lt;/code&gt;, but alas, I&#39;m stil stuck in the realm of linux.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where was I? Oh yes, I do have &lt;code&gt;org-capture&lt;/code&gt; templates set up that work just fine. I need to get the popup capture buffer to take the whole frame, though. I don&#39;t like that it also visits the capture buffer in the originally opened frame as well. It&#39;s an annoyance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m sure there should be more. I think I&#39;m going to wait until I&#39;ve got more, eh, content, here before I get various rss feeds set up for feeding into some of my social sites. I feel that I should probably &amp;quot;own my social&amp;quot;, too, and I do have at least one I run - but it&#39;s certainly a chore. We shall see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, I&#39;m out.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Good grief and all the gravy</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/good-grief-and-all-the-gravy/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-03T20:32:52+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/good-grief-and-all-the-gravy/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;more-site-updates&quot;&gt;More site updates &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#more-site-updates&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I&#39;ve added another section to the olde interweb presence: &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/drops&quot;&gt;Drops&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;What are drops?&amp;quot; I can hear absolutely nobody asking...well, I&#39;m glad you asked! Basically they&#39;re my &lt;em&gt;Read It Later&lt;/em&gt; links that I use some other web service to save for me - both the actual link, the data on the page, content and all that jazzy stuff. It&#39;s a service that I actually - shock! awe! - pay for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;d like to have all of that data &lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt; on this site - well, I guess it&#39;d be in the github repo, but still. As it is, I grab the latest 25 entries and display them on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/drops&quot;&gt;drops&lt;/a&gt; page. I suppose at some point in time I&#39;ll actually build in some kind of link roll or link blog or whatever, that way I can have the actual history in my site - but for now this is fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It took me way, &lt;strong&gt;way&lt;/strong&gt; too stinking long to get the secrets info dealt with for the github action. Too many tangents and too many wrong turns. But things seem to be working now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time for some breakage I think.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Oh for crying out loud!</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/oh-for-crying-out-loud!/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-04T17:37:14+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/oh-for-crying-out-loud!/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;all-i-can-do-is...&quot;&gt;All I can do is... &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#all-i-can-do-is...&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just sigh. In the realm of household appliances, my luck has not generally been very good. Let&#39;s just head straight into our latest little issue. We have (had? still have?) a Samsung Dryer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most of you who are (not?) out there, you may or may not know that Samsung makes a really shoddy piece of junk for a dryer. The drums in them like to crack and the rollers basically destroy themselves. It&#39;s a major issue, and they are basically ignoring the problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we purchased a new set, that is not Samsung. The delivery was this morning, but naturally did not get to go as planned. Something to do with the water shutoff valve not cooperating with the cold water. Yippee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just can&#39;t even, right now.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>More Updates and Stuff!</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/more-updates-and-stuff!/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-05T20:42:04+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/more-updates-and-stuff!/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;more-things-added-around-here&quot;&gt;More things added around here &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#more-things-added-around-here&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve added my &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/links&quot;&gt;links&lt;/a&gt; page now, along with a super nifty bookmarklet that I can use to add new links from the browser. I&#39;m sure that if anybody were to do any kind of digging on the interweb, they&#39;d know where I was able to grab some of the implementation details from. Of course, we all make our own nifty little changes, and I was no different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For one, I don&#39;t like a bunch of folders and &lt;em&gt;index.html&lt;/em&gt; files all over the place - so that had to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing that I&#39;ve noticed, here in the land of emacs, is that my capture session seems to have run into some interesting kinks. Oh, I bet it didn&#39;t like the &lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt; I used in the filename...what was I thinking!?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;where-was-i%3F&quot;&gt;Where was I? &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#where-was-i%3F&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh yes - I wanted to kind of explain my thinking on having &lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/drops&quot;&gt;drops&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/links&quot;&gt;links&lt;/a&gt;. To me, the &lt;em&gt;drops&lt;/em&gt; are for pages that I want to ensure never go away. A &lt;em&gt;read it later&lt;/em&gt;, if you will. The service I use (&lt;a href=&quot;https://raindrop.io/&quot;&gt;raindrop.io&lt;/a&gt;), takes care of that for me since I&#39;m a subscriber. &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/links&quot;&gt;Links&lt;/a&gt;, on the other hand, I don&#39;t care if those stick around or not. Plus, those actually get saved as files in the repo, as opposed to the drops, which are ephemeral data from the ether.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s my thinking, anyhow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All said and done, I think for now I&#39;m more or less finished with the structure of the site. Now, I just need more content - which will come with time. Then I can set up paging with whatever needs it. That, and get some rss feeds finalized, along with cross posting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Till next time.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Sometimes one wonders</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/sometimes-one-wonders/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-08T18:20:28+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/sometimes-one-wonders/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;for-crying-out-loud&quot;&gt;For Crying Out Loud &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#for-crying-out-loud&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m sure that I&#39;m not alone in this wondering, when sometimes it seems as though all the cards, all the world - heck &lt;em&gt;all the cards in all the world&lt;/em&gt; just seem to be lined up against you. These past couple of weeks have been a grand example of that for this household.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had purchased a certain brand (&lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt; Samsung &lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt;) washer and dryer. Said brand evidently makes really crappy dryer drums that like to crack and break and basically vomit all over themselves. They don&#39;t admit this, of course, and they aren&#39;t taking care of the problem. So we bought another brand in a single stacked unit. Because ours is a household that is very OCD about having things be the same. Plus, the stacked unit has the controls in the middle for the short people in the home. Plus we now have a little extra storage room in the washer and dryer room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first couple of guys who delivered the unit weren&#39;t the brightest bulbs in the garden. They either didn&#39;t know how to unhook the old units, or didn&#39;t know that &amp;quot;Yes, Alice, there is going to be a little water that leaks out of the old hose&amp;quot;. So they wouldn&#39;t finish the install, leaving the new unit in our garage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast forward to today, we get the old units removed and the new unit in place. Yes! Oh, what&#39;s this? The power cord goes from the top far corner of the unit and is about two (2) feet too stinking short?! No!! Dammit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;misery-is-a-beast&quot;&gt;Misery is a beast &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#misery-is-a-beast&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah. So, we were super stoked to get the new unit. Now we&#39;re basically at the point where we don&#39;t even wanna see the flipping thing in the home. But there it is, mocking us. Just sitting there, all unplugged. Laughing at us. No place in town sells a 10 foot four prong dryer cord. Now, we wait for the order from our saviour...amazon. Ugh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We really were hoping to get some laundry done today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;on-the-bright-side&quot;&gt;On the bright side &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#on-the-bright-side&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We did get to see some of the eclipse today! So much better than 2017, when it was terribly cloudy and overcast. This one reminded me of when I was in high school (mid 90s) and we also got to experience an eclipse. Very cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that - until next time.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Another Day Down</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-down/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-10T17:30:14+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-down/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;yeah-it&#39;s-my-rambling-series%2C-so-what%3F&quot;&gt;Yeah It&#39;s My Rambling Series, So What? &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#yeah-it&#39;s-my-rambling-series%2C-so-what%3F&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it&#39;s one thing that I&#39;ve noticed of late, it&#39;s that I must really enjoy rambling about nothing in particular. I suppose that&#39;s fine, of course, because it&#39;s good practice for any &lt;em&gt;actual&lt;/em&gt; writing that might come from this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, I think that we all know there we never be any &lt;em&gt;actual, real&lt;/em&gt; writing on this site. Who am I fooling, anyway?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;last-time-on...&quot;&gt;Last Time On... &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#last-time-on...&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When last we joined in the great adventures of &lt;em&gt;nobody in particular&lt;/em&gt; we had the washer and dryer in place. Not running or working, mind you. Because life is a fickle little something or other. I don&#39;t know who was in charge, or what they were smoking, or even what was running through their mind when it was decided by the powers that be that it was all &amp;quot;A Okay&amp;quot; to ship a meager six foot dryer power cord along with a pre-stacked washer and dryer unit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Especially when the electrical connection is at the upper back (we&#39;ll call it the upper right corner, looking at the thing from the back side) of the over six foot tall unit. Can you guess where I&#39;m going here? Our laundry room is set up to accommodate side by side units. As I would wager most peoples&#39; places are. Normally, this is not a problem. The power cord they ship (which, we have to purchase, naturally) didn&#39;t reach the dryer plug outlet on the wall by, oh, six inches. Not that it matters how short it was - it just flat out didn&#39;t reach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course nobody in town has a replacement dryer cord that we could pick up the same day. So, as we&#39;ve already read, we got one from amazon. A nice, ten footer. It reached no problem. All said and done, installed, working great! Finally, clean clothes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;state-of-my-blog&quot;&gt;State Of My Blog &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#state-of-my-blog&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve made some changes on the linkages up top, as well as the intro paragraph on the homearea page. I even have a newly opened branch where I&#39;ve got David Darnes &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/daviddarnes/mastodon-post/tree/main&quot;&gt;mastodon-post&lt;/a&gt; Web Component up and running (with a nod towards &lt;a href=&quot;https://coryd.dev/posts/2024/automatic-mastodon-post-embeds/&quot;&gt;Cory Dransfeldt&#39;s&lt;/a&gt; set up as well). It needs some love and I&#39;m not sure it&#39;ll ever go live, I don&#39;t know. I&#39;d want to perchance get a shortcode template set up to make it simpler for my needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, we&#39;ll call that an entry. I think I&#39;m doing a little better, I might even expand my writing to more than waxing about this silly site that I&#39;m making.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>My Eleventy Inspirations</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/my-eleventy-inspirations/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-11T18:10:44+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/my-eleventy-inspirations/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;where-i&#39;ve-drawn-inspiration-from&quot;&gt;Where I&#39;ve drawn inspiration from &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#where-i&#39;ve-drawn-inspiration-from&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I figure that this is as good a time as any to make some sort of attempt at getting down on &amp;quot;paper&amp;quot; those sites that I&#39;ve looked at and drawn some sort of inspiration from in the creation of my site. Not that my site is anything special, but it&#39;ll be good for the hypothetical &lt;em&gt;future me&lt;/em&gt; to be able to go back and see where things have come from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Granted, it&#39;s possible that a lot of these are also noted under my Eleventy &lt;a href=&quot;http://raindrop.io/&quot;&gt;Raindrop.io&lt;/a&gt; collection, but, you know - content and stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This page will probably be something of a living page for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
ul { list-style-position: outside; }
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/yinkakun/eleventy-duo&quot;&gt;The Site Theme.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s clean and I like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ttntm.me/blog/creating-a-reading-list-with-eleventy-and-omnivore/&quot;&gt;Creating a Reading List&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was very useful in some of the ideas of my drops page and similar. I also really like some of the other ideas that present themselves throughout the site in general - such as the main homepage landing area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simoncox.com/shorts/2024-03-17-11ty-collection-tag-links/&quot;&gt;11ty collections tag links&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some implementation info on collections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nicolas-hoizey.com/articles/2023/02/08/a-bookmarklet-to-create-a-new-link-content-markdown-on-github/&quot;&gt;A bookmarklet to create a new link content Markdown on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used for the bookmarklet to add a new link entry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://another.rodeo/linkroll/&quot;&gt;11ty Linkrolls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used in conjunction with the above to roll my own link roll page. (See what I did there?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raymondcamden.com/2022/03/08/including-rss-content-in-your-eleventy-site&quot;&gt;Including RSS Content&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raymondcamden.com/2022/04/03/including-rss-content-in-your-eleventy-site-part-2&quot;&gt;...and part 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using rss-parser and some other details with pulling rss data into a site. Plus, Raymond has an amazingly large amount of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raymondcamden.com/tags/eleventy&quot;&gt;eleventy tagged&lt;/a&gt; content on his site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;now-for-stuff-that-i&#39;d-like-to-consider-for-future-reference%3A&quot;&gt;Now for stuff that I&#39;d like to consider for future reference: &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#now-for-stuff-that-i&#39;d-like-to-consider-for-future-reference%3A&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/lwojcik/eleventy-template-multiplicity/tree/main&quot;&gt;Multiplicity Theme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This I really wouldn&#39;t mind including as an RSS reader/source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rknight.me/blog/using-eleventy-to-gobble-up-everything-i-do-online/&quot;&gt;Using Eleventy to Gobble Up Everything I Do Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author of this page also is the creator of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/rknightuk/echo&quot;&gt;Echo service&lt;/a&gt; (both for self host and hosted), and I am considering using that to enable posting on other social platforms as well. That said, this site is a great resource for pulling in other sources of data into Eleventy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coryd.dev/&quot;&gt;Cory Dransfeldt&#39;s Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just lots of good content here, including &lt;a href=&quot;https://coryd.dev/posts/2024/automatic-mastodon-post-embeds/&quot;&gt;embedding mastodon posts.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://darn.es/mastodon-post-web-component/&quot;&gt;mastodon-post web component&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From David Darnes, this component used within the previous link. I do have a branch of my site that uses this, but I&#39;m not put it into production yet. I&#39;m up in the air about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nhoizey/github-action-feed-to-mastodon&quot;&gt;Github Action Feed to Mastodon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sends json sourced feed into a Mastodon instance. This is also referenced from the previous set of links, though I don&#39;t believe it&#39;s a requirement on its own. This could - possibly? - be superceded by Echo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://11tybundle.dev/firehose/&quot;&gt;11tybundle.dev firehose&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anything and everything 11ty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sia.codes/tags/eleventy/&quot;&gt;Sia dot Codes Eleventy Items&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another popular and excellent source of information on the eleventy&#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://11ty.rocks/community/&quot;&gt;11ty Rocks! Community Feed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some good entries from around the horn here, plus some other valuable posts as well of their own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.lukaszwojcik.net/eleventy-custom-markup-alongside-item-contents/&quot;&gt;Eleventy: custom markup alongside item contents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nifty use of markdown and customization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Not another new server</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-another-new-server/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-17T21:17:08+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-another-new-server/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h2 id=&quot;another-fediverse-server%3F!&quot;&gt;Another Fediverse Server?! &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#another-fediverse-server%3F!&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, I don&#39;t have &lt;em&gt;yet another fediverse server instance&lt;/em&gt; stood up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not for some lack of trying, mind you, I just don&#39;t have the energy to put into working through all the nits and nats that are involved with ruby. I shudder to think. I&#39;ve never really been a huge fan of that whole ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s not as bad as the JavaScript world, but it&#39;s not fun to navigate for me either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was wanting to get a &lt;a href=&quot;https://diasporafoundation.org/&quot;&gt;Diaspora&lt;/a&gt; instance set up on a digital ocean droplet, but decided against it. Then, to follow along in some other rabbit hole, I signed up on Yet Another ActivityPub Instance, in the form of &lt;a href=&quot;https://akkomane.social/@shane&quot;&gt;Akkomane Social&lt;/a&gt;. It seems nice, thus far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news, yeah - it&#39;s been a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s also only Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Just a handful of notes please</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/just-a-handful-of-notes-please/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-22T21:04:04+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/just-a-handful-of-notes-please/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;We shall go ahead and tag this one into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/rambling&quot;&gt;rambling&lt;/a&gt; series, why not? Kind of a small update of a few things that have happened over the course of the last couple of days I suppose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;i&#39;m-really-bad-a-blogging&quot;&gt;I&#39;m really bad a blogging &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#i&#39;m-really-bad-a-blogging&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Point taken, I&#39;m not really good at sitting down and getting something on digital paper every single day. Granted, I&#39;m not good at sitting down and getting something put on actual real paper, either. At least I&#39;m equal opportunity when it comes to writing. Which I find a little sad, since it is something that I enjoy doing. I&#39;m trying, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The end of last week was really good, though. Our twins performed in one of the local plays and three of the performances were last Thursday, Friday and Saturday. I (well, my spouse and I both) are beyond proud of them (again, all of our kids, actually) for doing things that I could never have even thought of doing when I was their age. &amp;quot;What, get up on stage and act?! No thank you.&amp;quot; I&#39;m very, very introverted. The thought of doing a play (or musical!) would petrify me. The musical they did as well, earlier in the year, so yeah!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They did exceedingly well. I can not brag on my kids enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;i&#39;m-also-bad-at-reading-self-help-books&quot;&gt;I&#39;m also bad at reading self help books &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#i&#39;m-also-bad-at-reading-self-help-books&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, not that I have a whole &lt;strong&gt;lot&lt;/strong&gt; of self help books, but I have picked up a couple of them that really interested me. I&#39;d found a hardback copy of &lt;em&gt;William Zinsser&#39;s Writing to Learn&lt;/em&gt;, which just seemed very cool and might perhaps help out with this personal site of mine. Guess how much of it I&#39;ve read? A couple of pages. But enough I know that I think I&#39;ll really like the style. Ha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, I finally got my copy of &lt;em&gt;Brain Hacks&lt;/em&gt;, by &lt;em&gt;Lara Honos-Webb&lt;/em&gt;, which seems like it could help with some organizational skills that frankly any of us could use. It was actually recommended to one of the previously mentioned twins above that he should read it for one of his projects. So he is. I don&#39;t know that he&#39;s gotten much out of it - but hopefully more than I have, as I&#39;ve read an astounding two pages in it. Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;i&#39;m-better-at-reading-for-enjoyment&quot;&gt;I&#39;m better at reading for enjoyment &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#i&#39;m-better-at-reading-for-enjoyment&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will admit, that I do actually enjoy reading and am continuing to work my way through &lt;em&gt;The Expanse&lt;/em&gt; novels. Currently reading &lt;em&gt;Nemesis Games&lt;/em&gt; in what spare time I can steal. I&#39;m also reading &lt;em&gt;The Dark Elf Trilogy&lt;/em&gt; to at least one of the twins, we just got into the second book the other week. This is the second go through of this series for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;other-news%3F&quot;&gt;Other news? &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#other-news%3F&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I always feel like I should put something down about the current state of this site. I don&#39;t know why. I&#39;m happy with it, but not really super happy with it. I guess it&#39;s a great medium to just be able to get words down. I don&#39;t really care too much for the theme or the look of the site, but then I don&#39;t have the time to put into making it any better. I&#39;d like to do more with webmentions and other indieweb stuff - but then I also don&#39;t do a whole lot with social media, period. It&#39;s tough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like to write, I&#39;ll continue to write, whether or not people read really doesn&#39;t concern me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ll leave it at that.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>And Now For Something Different</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/and-now-for-something-different/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-29T20:29:44+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/and-now-for-something-different/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Ah and now for something (not so?) completely different! For those of you who have been following along at home - which, I suppose, would really just be me, myself and I - I&#39;ve made some changes to the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No longer is the static site based on Eleventy Duo. Welcome, instead, to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/google/eleventy-high-performance-blog&quot;&gt;eleventy high performance blog&lt;/a&gt;. Being a tinkerer does at times really, really suck. Never being happy or content with the way things are on the old blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The change actually went a lot smoother than I was anticipating it going. I cloned the new template to a clean directory. Made the changes that I needed to make to it (at least, started them - I&#39;m sure more will come). Renamed the remote origin and added a new remote origin. Then, over in my now old and stale github repo I renamed the &#39;main&#39; branch, added a new &#39;to migrate&#39; branch, then went back to the new template and did the ol&#39; something of a force push to the new branch on my static site repo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once that was done, I had to rename the local and remote repos back to main and set the new default branch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, things still just worked after that! Had to make a single change to the emacs org capture template to ensure the directory for the posts was good...now, I think we&#39;re golden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or at least a decent shade of pale yellow.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Weblog Posting Month 2024</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/weblog-posting-month-2024/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-29T21:29:26+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/weblog-posting-month-2024/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;I think I&#39;m going to try to do something that will be very difficult for me. I&#39;ve decided to join the group in a &lt;em&gt;post every day during the month of May&lt;/em&gt; challenge that has been dubbed &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;#WeblogPoMo2024&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I shall be using the same tag here, &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;as well&lt;/a&gt; for sake of categorization. I guess it&#39;s likely  that I&#39;ll even start using the echo feed account that I&#39;ve been paying for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ll see how this goes. I was able to do the &amp;quot;post a photo every day for 30 days&amp;quot; thing over on microblog to get that badge, which wasn&#39;t super easy for me either.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Things I&#39;m Learning</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/things-i&amp;#39;m-learning/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-30T15:26:37+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/things-i&amp;#39;m-learning/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;For those of you who follow my pixelfed feed, you may have seen the following image&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe title=&quot;Pixelfed Post Embed&quot; src=&quot;https://pixelfed.social/p/swrogers/690632497756857978/embed?caption=false&amp;likes=false&amp;layout=compact&quot; class=&quot;pixelfed__embed&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%; border: 0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;allowfullscreen&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; defer=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://pixelfed.social/embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it&#39;s only tangentially related to what I do at work, it&#39;s something that is actively encouraged for us to do - continue to learn. I figure since I am around Oracle Databases all the time, I should probably widen my breadth of knowledge a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who knows, I might even be able to add to my repertoire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;possible-future-notes-to-self&quot;&gt;Possible future notes to self &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#possible-future-notes-to-self&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m wondering how feasible it might be to have echofeed (perhaps) cross post from pixelfed into this github pages hosted site. I know I could do an rss feed pull. Of course, then I&#39;d need some way to ensure that doubled (or more...) posts aren&#39;t sent out via echofeed to the mastodon account. I&#39;m sure that other people have solved this issue, though. Heh.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Writing to learn - Weblog Posting Month 2024</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/writing-to-learn-weblog-posting-month-2024/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-01T16:19:52+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/writing-to-learn-weblog-posting-month-2024/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Well it&#39;s finally here: my first entry into Annie&#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Weblog PoMo 2024&lt;/a&gt;. As with most things that I do when it comes to writing, I haven&#39;t really planned this out. Does that mean that I&#39;m most likely going to fail at it? That is a definite possibility. But I&#39;m willing to at least give it a shot for myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, there is nothing like getting an &lt;a href=&quot;https://echofeed.app/&quot;&gt;Echofeed&lt;/a&gt; set up for it to help with some accountability - up to and including having the &lt;a href=&quot;https://beep.town/@echofeedamplify&quot;&gt;Amplify Bot&lt;/a&gt; boost your stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that out of the way, let&#39;s get the ball rolling on &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;writing-to-learn&quot;&gt;Writing to learn &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#writing-to-learn&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or something like that. Writing to learn, writing to keep yourself accountable, whatever the reason it&#39;s a good skill to have. It&#39;s not necessarily something that one actually appreciates when they are younger. I graduated high school in 1995 and was fortunate enough to have had a couple of college level courses that we were able to take during our senior year - including an English course that included at least one paper. It was a great start on my college and university stint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I did eventually enroll and find myself in college, part of our curriculum was a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Writing_across_the_curriculum&quot;&gt;Writing to learn&lt;/a&gt; selection of courses - I believe that we needed required to take two or three of these. The idea - at the time at least - was something that I can&#39;t say I was too overly fond of. I was going to be a Computer Science major and didn&#39;t feel that I needed to &amp;quot;Write to Learn&amp;quot;. Of course, I did though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wouldn&#39;t be until much, &lt;strong&gt;much&lt;/strong&gt; later that I would find the source of this sound reasoning: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.harpercollins.com/products/writing-to-learn-william-zinsser?variant=42347013505058&quot;&gt;William Zinsser&#39;s Book&lt;/a&gt;. At least, I assume this to be the source. My plan, my goal, is to actually read this book. I don&#39;t think it to be too much to ask. I&#39;ve already got one chapter down and I find that I really like the flow and the style. So, part of what I write about this month is going to include some of my thoughts on the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t going to be some great article series, no doubt about that. But I do hope that I&#39;m able to improve a bit on my writing, maybe it can even become a habit to write more. I don&#39;t think I could hope to be able to write &lt;em&gt;better&lt;/em&gt;, I find that I&#39;m pretty well stuck in my ways on that account.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will end this entry with a bit of an anecdote. Not long after I moved to Lawrence, I found myself sitting at a local restaurant eating a meal. Behind me sat a couple of who I will assume to be professors from the university and they were having a conversation. The subject of students not knowing how to write papers came up, which was kind of a surprise to me. This was quite some time ago, but from what I can recall I do remember thinking to myself how sad and disturbing that was. How could students in this (that?) day and age make it through high school and into college or university and not know how to write?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can only imagine that now, it&#39;s a problem that has not gotten any better. Writing is becoming a lost art it seems.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Another Day, Another Chapter. Day Two.</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-another-chapter.-day-two./"/>
		<updated>2024-05-02T14:00:56+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-another-chapter.-day-two./</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;The second day brings with it a second chapter of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.harpercollins.com/products/writing-to-learn-william-zinsser?variant=42347013505058&quot;&gt;Writing To Learn&lt;/a&gt; book. To be completely fair, I had read about half of this yesterday and have finished it up this morning. To be even more fair, it will be highly probable that I&#39;ll read chapter 3 and add more to this post today as well. Let us find out what has been digested this go round, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;gustavus-adolphus-college&quot;&gt;Gustavus Adolphus College &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#gustavus-adolphus-college&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right out of the gate I learned something. While even the author, Zinsser, did believe that everybody should be able to write - he did literally write the book on the subject - the idea of &lt;em&gt;Writing Across the Curriculum&lt;/em&gt; came from the small Midwestern College of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gustavus_Adolphus_College&quot;&gt;Gustavus Adolphus&lt;/a&gt;. Or, at least as well as I can tell according to the text. Even at that point in history (jeeze, only 1985) the professors had a need and a want to move the responsibility of teaching students to write away from the &amp;quot;English&amp;quot; Department. Which makes complete sense to me. We write - or should write - about more than just, well, previously written materials (books, plays, what have you). Noted within this chapter are numerous other great sources of written material - from beautiful mathematic proofs, to how the periodic table of the elements are arranged and why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-puzzle-of-the-humanities&quot;&gt;A puzzle of the humanities &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#a-puzzle-of-the-humanities&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An interesting point was brought up during my reading today. If one&#39;s mind likes to work though puzzles, finding solutions to whatever has been presented to you, then perhaps no matter what the subject matter is it could be possible to find an intriguing route to write about said solution. As an example, the author has noted multiple times that they did not care for chemistry in school. Maybe if some of the work had been phrased the way that &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dmitri_Mendeleev&quot;&gt;D I Mendeleev&lt;/a&gt; had worked out the &lt;em&gt;Periodic Law&lt;/em&gt; and creating a version of the &lt;em&gt;Period Table of the Elements&lt;/em&gt;, then that challenge would have had a more positive effect on him. If there is some way to find a human element to whatever subject matter is being studied or written about, that seems to help a great deal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-feeling-of-rambling&quot;&gt;A feeling of rambling &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#a-feeling-of-rambling&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m doing it again - I feel like I&#39;m just kind of rambling on. I should tighten this stuff up. Meh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us finish up with a couple of quotes from the chapter that have kind of stuck with me:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Students should be learning a strong and unpretentious prose that will carry their thoughts about the world they live in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...every subject is interesting if an avenue into it can be found that has humanity and that an ordinary person can follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These ring well with me. I&#39;m no journalist, no professional writer for sure. But I have read a wide variety of subjects, books, magazines, articles...those that leave the best impression are of the style that don&#39;t belittle or &amp;quot;talk down&amp;quot; to the reader. I find it sad that today we are losing a large amount of written work that may never be. Amazing magazines that have stopped printing. Journals that are no longer around. Yes, I am aware of the irony that any readers of this material are doing so on a media that involves a screen. It&#39;s easier, but only in so many ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The challenge is finding it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Here we go day three</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/here-we-go-day-three/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-03T19:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/here-we-go-day-three/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;It&#39;s day three of Weblog Posting Month 2024!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whew!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ll be honest, I was beginning to wonder if I was going to make it today. Today has been challenging, to say the least, so I will be putting off today&#39;s reading of the &amp;quot;Writing to Learn&amp;quot; book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Why is that?&amp;quot; - I hear absolutely noone asking. Well, I&#39;ll tell you anyhow. I do much of my blog posting through &lt;code&gt;emacs&lt;/code&gt; using &lt;code&gt;org-mode&lt;/code&gt; capture templates. My current &lt;code&gt;emacs&lt;/code&gt; configuration is a semi modified &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/doomemacs/doomemacs&quot;&gt;doom emacs&lt;/a&gt; build which has worked very well for me in the past and continues to do so in the present. Generally. I don&#39;t know if I had some kind of hardware issue (which is possible, as my config is hosted on a local NAS with used drives) due to perhaps a recent storm, but my org capture templates were just not working at all. Even after a &lt;code&gt;doom doctor&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;doom purge&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;doom build&lt;/code&gt; cycle...nothing worked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which necessitated a &lt;em&gt;nuclear option&lt;/em&gt; of a fresh git checkout of doom and starting over. It&#39;s not really a complete do over, though, since I still have my private/personal doom init files that live in a different directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, after about an hour and ten minutes of waiting for the build process to finish (ugh...) we are back to par. Yippee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-actual-challenge&quot;&gt;The actual challenge &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#the-actual-challenge&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything stated, I have actually read a bit of the next chapter, and all of the above was initiated because I wanted to take a handful of notes. One item in particular, about clear writing being evidence of clear thinking. Something of which I really need to strive to do - think clearly. With that, and just a little bit of focus, perhaps I can write clearly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#WeblogPoMo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Day Four, Nothing More</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/day-four-nothing-more/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-04T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/day-four-nothing-more/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Here we are at day for during this monthly challenge. The next couple of days are going to be the first two that present as very difficult for me - will I be able to get something posted during the weekend, while the home is filled with family and kids and I would rather &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; be dealing with a computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So in that case, I am not using a computer or laptop for the post. Instead I&#39;m seeing how well the &lt;a href=&quot;https://gitjournal.io/&quot;&gt;GitJournal&lt;/a&gt; app works on my phone. I don&#39;t really have any other content management system set up here, so this really needs to work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe this would be a good excuse to set up a Ghost CMS for the front end. Probably not, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve done no reading today, so that&#39;s a negative. I did check out the Samurai Jack series from the local library, I&#39;m looking forward to giving that a watch!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that....till next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#Weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>It&#39;s the fifth day</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/it&amp;#39;s-the-fifth-day/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-05T20:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/it&amp;#39;s-the-fifth-day/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;This is the fifth day of the challenge! Yesterday was an attempt to post something using the GitJournal app, which sort of worked, but didn&#39;t work quite as smoothly as one would have liked. It failed to save the new file in the appropriate folder, though I&#39;m fairly certain I saved it where it needed. Then when trying to move it, it does a copy instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which plays havoc with the push to git and the workflow run. Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, in my attempt to both come up with a post today &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; perhaps a decent mobile way to post, today is just straight into the github web site and add a new post. Is it preferable? Absolutely not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news today, I was able to get the yard mowed before it rained. I&#39;ve got this feeling that for the next month or so it&#39;s basically going to be &amp;quot;mow whenever you flippin&#39; can&amp;quot;. Otherwise, my old battery operated Snapper just - literally - isn&#39;t going to cut it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, off to the store. Tonight is homemade tomato soup and grilled cheese with smoked gouda. Perhaps a tasty antipasto salad as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A day of waxing philosophically</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-day-of-waxing-philosophically/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-06T20:00:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-day-of-waxing-philosophically/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;It&#39;s day the next around these parts. For whatever that means, right? I&#39;ve not made nearly the progress on my book that I&#39;d like to, so today&#39;s entry will be another one of those &amp;quot;day in the life of&amp;quot; ordeals. I might even be able to make this interesting, but I wouldn&#39;t let odds down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year I turn 47. Not quite the same as when one turns 40, though let&#39;s be honest here, I don&#39;t think my 40th was anything all that spectacular. Nor is it quite the same as turning 50, I&#39;m guessing. As I get older and watch my kids get older, I can&#39;t help but think that it really wasn&#39;t all that much long ago that I was their age, almost in their shoes, going through similar phases. I&#39;ve tried to do my absolute best buy my kids. My Dad, who I love, has probably told me that he loves me only a handful of times. I know he does, but I&#39;ve tried to reverse that trend with my boys.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think back to some of the points in my life, I try to correlate how old my kiddo&#39;s are, to how old I was, to how old my Dad was (or, would have been at that time). I always wonder what would have been going through his mind. It&#39;s just strange, trying to put myself into his place. There are differences between the two of us, there is no doubt there. As parents, we try to ensure that our children have access to things that we never had - or, in my case things that I never knew that I should have or would have wanted. Things as simple as high school yearbooks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn&#39;t go to a large high school, nor did I have an over abundance of friends, nor did I ever think that I would want to ever reminisce about those years of my life. Of course, growing up I think I must have thought that yearbooks just magically showed up at school on yearbook signing day. It never would have occurred to me that there was an (at times) significant cost involved. My kids may not realize it now, but they&#39;ll be thankful for those, at least, in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, we love our kids and want the best for them. Though, what parent does not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, with that I think we shall close out this day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the rest of my &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>And on the seventh day</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/and-on-the-seventh-day/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-07T18:00:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/and-on-the-seventh-day/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Aye, and on the seventh day yet another post has appeared! We are coming up on the end of another school year for our kids, another year that continues to speed on past us. The next few weeks are going to be very full of events. Along with the full schedules, comes special types of stress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stress. Along with most people, I would imagine, I am not a fan. Some people stress eat, thankfully I am not one of those. I eat out of boredom. At least this is something that I am aware of. I&#39;ve been trying to eat better for a handful of years now, some would say successfully. My wife and myself opted to go the ketogenic journey and I have kept a out 145 pounds off my frame for some time now. Three thirty plus to one eighty five, give or take.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, so where am I going in all of this rambling? As I get older, as I watch my kids grow into greater ages, I made a decision that I wanted to see them get older. I knew that if I had continued on in the direction that I was going, that I&#39;d be in a grave within very little time. I have no doubt that I have avoided diabetes and at least taken one foot off of the banana peel, so to speak. Not to mention feeling much better and, hopefully, modeling a healthier behavior for my children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No rest for myself on this day, though. The second day of my vacation and I&#39;ve done little to nothing that I would like to get done. Ah, but then who really wants to do pre-spring cleaning on their vacations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read the rest of my &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The Eighth Day is an Early Day</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-eighth-day-is-an-early-day/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-08T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-eighth-day-is-an-early-day/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;It&#39;s the eighth day of the month. I got to drop the older two boys off for zero hour honor choir a little early this morning, 6:50AM instead of 7:00AM. One wouldn&#39;t think that 10 minutes would make much of a difference, but it certainly can. We did get there in time, so yay. Of course, for me just being some place &lt;em&gt;on time&lt;/em&gt; actually means that &lt;em&gt;I&#39;m late&lt;/em&gt;. Now, if I could only get my spouse to adhere to that philosophy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning, and tomorrow morning, will both be basically the same. The twins have a music performance on Friday that is the big finale for the year. Tonight we also have a band concert for one of them. Like I said the other day, it&#39;s gonna be a full week. It &lt;em&gt;has been&lt;/em&gt; a full week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;mobile-editing&quot;&gt;Mobile editing &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#mobile-editing&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I may have finally found a decent markdown editor that can sync with my git blog repo: &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.eu.thedoc.zettelnotes&quot;&gt;Zettel Notes&lt;/a&gt;. Well, sure, there have been others that can sync and work, but I think I really prefer this one for some reason. Probably because it can actually move files around when requested as opposed to copying them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the only thing that I would like to be able to do from mobile (apart from easier photo uploads, but someday maybe) would be running the eleventy test server. Other than that, I&#39;m pretty content with what&#39;s available now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Another day another waste</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-another-waste/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-09T17:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/another-day-another-waste/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;I think that I&#39;ve come to where I would much rather be working. Work is enjoyable, vacations are nothing but just waiting to to back to work. It&#39;s not so much a dread for the end of the vacation, but just knowing that I never am able to accomplish what I would like to do during the time away from work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not that I&#39;m disparaging the vacation. I&#39;m equal opportunity when it comes to not being a fan of not working, I&#39;m not really big on weekends either. Granted I&#39;d probably to absolutely insane if I did nothing but work. One has to have some time off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where I work, we get plenty of paid leave to earn. Eight hours per every Eighty hour work period, up to a maximum of 304 hours. Of which I am routinely butted up against. Plus, a discretionary holiday. I really should take more time for myself, I&#39;m told multiple times by multiple people that I should.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, alas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current question then becomes, do I feel that anything has been accomplished during this break. There was some yardwork done. The car was washed, by hand, even! I may have gotten the yard mowed once. It just always feels like there is something that needs to be done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Sponges and Splashes</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/sponges-and-splashes/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-10T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/sponges-and-splashes/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;My original idea for this month, the challenge of posting a &amp;quot;simple&amp;quot; blog post each day, was to have myself read the &amp;quot;Writing to Learn&amp;quot; book and then give my thoughts on what I had read. This far, I have only succeeded at half of that challenge, having not really made much progress in the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do say that I&#39;m not really all that surprised. I did take this week off of work, so did my spouse. Therefore I just don&#39;t really have much in the way of a desire to sit, read and contemplate. What o have been able to do, though, in stealing away a few bits of time here and there to write, has been of good use. It&#39;s been not quite cathartic, but very close, to get words out of my head and onto the screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning was field day for the fifth grader. We signed up to assist the teachers with attempting to keep the students under some kind of control. Basically just ensuring that they didn&#39;t maim each other. I had myself stationed at what I&#39;ll refer to as the &lt;em&gt;sponge fighting&lt;/em&gt; location. One of the handful of water areas that are set up. The idea here being that the kids pair up and toss a sopping wet sponge back and forth. If you can&#39;t catch the sponge, then you wring it out over your head. It&#39;s all good fun. It all more or less kind of devolves into &amp;quot;let&#39;s just throw wet sponges at each other!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We go back shortly to help out with the Montessori primary group - the kindergartners. It should be a lot of fun. Our six year old is very excited to have us there with him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tonight is another performance, as well. The twins have the last major show for honor choir, which the class has been working towards for some time now. After that, then then of school. It&#39;s crazy, how quickly this year has gone by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It will soon be midsummer. Then it&#39;ll be turkey day. Then new years. Then...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Junk Food For Thought</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/junk-food-for-thought/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-11T20:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/junk-food-for-thought/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;It&#39;s the eleventh of May. Saturday. A day to do not a whole lot. Same as tomorrow I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been trying for most of the day to come up with some kind of theme for todays post. I guess it&#39;s been staring me in the face for the day as well, if only I could open the proverbial eyes. It has actually been making its path through my hands, in front of my face and down the old gullet multiple times today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s kind of funny, what is one person&#39;s junk food is not the same as every body else&#39;s junk food. What was junk food for me me years ago is completely off limits to me now, nor do I crave those items now. Thankfully. Today, my junk food is stuff like cheese, natural peanut butter, macadamia nuts. All high calorie stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we first started keto, I thought that must difficult things to give to would be all the baked goods: cookies, biscuits, cakes, etc. I mentally gamed it, though, and was able to conquer those cravings. My first hump was getting past 220 and into the so-called &lt;em&gt;one-derland&lt;/em&gt;. Now, that I&#39;ve been past there, into the 170s, my new plateau is trying to get back below 180. I&#39;ve continued to be in the 190s for longer than I like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really need to get back into that track, stop snacking, get away from the peanut butter and dairy, start tracking everything that goes on my plate once again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve started not feeling my best. I need to get there once again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Nothing to see here</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/nothing-to-see-here/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-12T20:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/nothing-to-see-here/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Today is the twelfth of May. The last day of my vacation, yet another vacation where absolutely nothing was accomplished. I&#39;d feel bad, but I generally don&#39;t get much done on these things. Who wants to work on their vacations. Normally I&#39;d take a pair of weeks off, which would at least enable me to sorta almost get something done during the second week. But not this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m sitting here at someone&#39;s home, of whom I have no idea who they are. Well, I guess it&#39;s a home, more a ranch. It&#39;s a really nice place. But, even then it&#39;s one of those deals where I don&#39;t know anyone here and really don&#39;t have much of a connection with anyone. All I can say and think is, &lt;em&gt;man, I couldn&#39;t even fathom owning this much land or this kind of property&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully we aren&#39;t going to be here long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;four-hours-later&quot;&gt;Four Hours Later &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#four-hours-later&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Give or take. It&#39;s after dinner, so it&#39;s time to catch up on some entertainment. Today it&#39;s &lt;strong&gt;Dead Boy Detectives&lt;/strong&gt;. I seem to recall something about a possible spin off of these characters with an episode of &lt;strong&gt;Doom Patrol&lt;/strong&gt;, but I could be wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far it&#39;s pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other news, &lt;em&gt;Happy Mother&#39;s Day&lt;/em&gt; to those that celebrate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Not So Triskaidekaphobic</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-so-triskaidekaphobic/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-13T23:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-so-triskaidekaphobic/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Lucky number thirteen!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wasn&#39;t too certain that I was going to make this one, if I were to be completely honest. It&#39;s been a day full of watching a sick kiddo and trying to keep myself in check as well. To say that it has not been a great day would be an understatement at the least.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve had a couple of really long nights, as our youngest has been making his way into our room (which is not so different from the normal) and coughing up a storm (which is different from the norm). Hopefully he&#39;ll be able to get this thing beat soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will say that I&#39;m lucky in that my job is very flexible in allowing us to e to care for family and self. I know that not everyone is so fortunate. For that, I am thankful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an aside, I have finally been able to watch &lt;strong&gt;Dune Part Two&lt;/strong&gt;, which was excellent. I had really wanted to see it in a theater but was never able to make it. The first &lt;strong&gt;Dune&lt;/strong&gt; was actually the he first movie I saw in the theater after the world had began to open back up. Some might say post COVID, but I think that we all know we are still current COVID. Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These entries have been good for just getting my mind settled and thawed out for the day. While nowhere near what I had intended to write about, I hope to be able to continue on this path. Whether anyone reads them or not, matters not to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Just for me</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/just-for-me/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-14T15:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/just-for-me/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Two weeks in, so far so good?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing that is certainly a bonus when participating in a weblog writing challenge is that one may just happen upon some other interesting writers or posts. Which is, I suppose, one of the reasons the challenge even exists. There have been multiple reasons - excuses really - for why I&#39;ve never done much writing for myself, the least of which being my internal thought that &lt;em&gt;I have nothing of interest for anyone to read&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah, but really though, is that the sole reason to write? No. I should write for myself, no matter how mundane I think the entry of the day will be. Have I been taking care of a child with a racking cough, who rends at my heart because there just isn&#39;t much that I can do for him? Yep, so I should write about that. Was I finally able to get some yardwork done because the incessant rain finally stopped? Yep, note it down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why shouldn&#39;t I go on and just use a blog as a daily journal. It takes zero effort at this point and it&#39;s for my own good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that might be interested, including future me, &lt;a href=&quot;https://brandons-journal.com/post/shame-and-blogging-redux&quot;&gt;here is the post that sparked&lt;/a&gt; this entry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s still early, so there may be more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;awards-and-stuff&quot;&gt;Awards and stuff &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#awards-and-stuff&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As parents we love to brag on our children. With five excellent young kiddos, I have no limit to the amount of praise that can be levied. Today has been no exception. We just returned from the fifth grader&#39;s surprise award presentation, where he received an Unsung Hero award from a local group. They choose two young students each year to honor, and we were pleasantly surprised when we found out he was chosen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kids are absolutely amazing and I look forward to seeing what they are able to accomplish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Catch up to the lifestyle</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/catch-up-to-the-lifestyle/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-15T18:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/catch-up-to-the-lifestyle/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;We seem to be nearing the midway point of the month. I am just getting back to work from a week of &amp;quot;vacation&amp;quot;, then two days of having a sick kiddo at home. Okay, so three days, really, but today has been more of a &amp;quot;letting the kiddo keep his temp normal&amp;quot; kinda day. Not so much sick, as he is stopped up. At least the cough is more or less done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As is the way of things, after taking a week off of work today has basically been spent playing catch-up. At least it hasn&#39;t been as bad as it&#39;s been in the past. Just a couple of quick answers that needed to be sent out. I&#39;m so glad this is a slower time of year. I&#39;ve generally taken two weeks off at a time, but figured I&#39;d change things up this go round. Of course, what with the sick kiddo I was beginning to wonder if I might have wound up taking this week off as sick leave too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-lifestyle&quot;&gt;The lifestyle &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#the-lifestyle&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How about an update on my keto life? My weight has been steadily creeping up over that 190 plus mark over the past few months. Certainly not where I want to be, no matter what other people in my life think. While I do agree that sub 170 is not a good look on me, I continue to struggle with making my way down below 190. I still have my goal at 182, preferably.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do consider myself lucky (accomplished?) in that I still wear the same sized jeans and clothes, so I haven&#39;t had to change or modify the wardrobe again. Thankfully. That&#39;s one of my major fears, that whole idea of relapse, once I were to allow myself to get comfortable with a weight. When that happens, then I stop logging all food, I start snacking more, I start thinking that eating this little bit of junk is going to be okay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then it&#39;s just a completely blown day and I wanna retreat within myself. I need to be able to string together a few good days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need this win, again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Not so messy this time</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-so-messy-this-time/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-16T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-so-messy-this-time/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;It&#39;s the afternoon and I&#39;m sitting in the car, waiting for the two youngest to get released from school. I can&#39;t complain about how the day has gone, it&#39;s been pretty good and relatively productive. I&#39;m just glad that the little one was able to go and stay at school all day! I love that my kids, generally, enjoy school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of my job role involves application upgrades for some decently large vendors, Oracle and Salesforce come to mind. These upgrades can be a tad kludgy. An understatement to say the least. I&#39;ve been through a handful of one upgrade in particular that I have been able to get documented fairly well, and I believe that I now have it down to, if not a science then at least an art. Art is still allowed to be messy - and this thing is no exception. I think my favorite part of this last patch cycle was that Oracle has evidently stopped providing (what appears to be) either a second copy of their jdk, or they&#39;ve streamlined it into a non-versioned directory. Which I suppose is nice. At least it was easy enough to sort out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve got some other projects in the hopper at work, and it feels good to be a part of them. It almost feels like progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah, the kids are picked up. Some garlic olives have been snacked on (it is weird how ones tastes change when away from carbohydrates for so long). I&#39;m sure I could ramble on more, but I think I&#39;m good here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading, if you are. If you&#39;re not, then that&#39;s okay too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A perfectly cromulent day</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-perfectly-cromulent-day/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-17T20:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-perfectly-cromulent-day/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;I feel like I should have more to write about today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like I could (should?) have been more productive today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let us count what all I&#39;ve accomplished to get done this fine, fine Friday the seventeenth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of our major SaaS applications is going to be upgraded at the end of the month, so that needed to be added to the calendar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A group request that I&#39;d made a couple of days ago was just fulfilled, so I was able to make a couple of updates in prep for a background process. Which can&#39;t be finished until a separate sync occurs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I brought an item to another groups attention, so that the requestor can be thought how to help themselves.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&#39;ve started learning a new service management/issue tracker/asset management/knowledge base system of which I am one of the main admins for our group. This should be fun.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trying to pick up some Laravel. I don&#39;t know why or for what purpose, seeing as I actually prefer clojure for fun and....well, not really profit seeing as how it&#39;s a hobby.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, that&#39;s about the gist of what I&#39;ve done today. I guess I did upgrade one of my Kimsufi boxes and portainer container. It&#39;s been a moderately full day, and for that I&#39;m completely okay!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A chore no more</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-chore-no-more/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-18T15:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-chore-no-more/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Ah, welcome to the weekend!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally was able to sleep in a bit this morning, all of until 8am. Still feels like sleeping half the morning away, though, especially when one is used to getting up at 6am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a Saturday it&#39;s been kinda productive, managed to get the lawn mowed for the first time in over a week. It&#39;s funny, when I was a kid and had to mow two yards and a large back lot I was never a fan of the chore. It could have had something to do with needing to deal with a black walnut tree....if you know, you know. Ugh. Now, though, it&#39;s a good time to unwind with some music and enjoy the process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Certainly it&#39;s not something that I&#39;d consider a chore. My yard doesn&#39;t look the best in the neighborhood, but at least it&#39;s far from the worst. I try to take at least a little bit of pride in how the home looks. It doesn&#39;t hurt that the neighbors also have really nice lawns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve got other things around the home that I&#39;d like to do - one of which being permanent holiday lighting with some programmable LEDs. Maybe I can tackle that project this Summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A title should go here</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-title-should-go-here/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-19T15:00:00+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-title-should-go-here/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;It&#39;s Sunday, which thankfully means that the weekend is nearly, blessedly, over. One of these days I&#39;ll figure out what it is about the weekend or time off that I don&#39;t care for. Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managed to get the dishwasher unloaded and reloaded this morning. Sometimes I still feel very much like that butter robot. Only I get to do more than just &amp;quot;pass the butter&amp;quot;, I also get to fetch fresh paper towel rolls from storage! Aren&#39;t I lucky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know that people don&#39;t take me for granted, but good grief sometimes it really does feel that way. Are there things in my life that I would haved changed, given the chance? Sure, I don&#39;t think that there is anybody out there that would say otherwise. I try to stay upbeat and somewhat optimistic, but it can be a challenge. Especially when you live with somebody who has depression. Anyhow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was going to write something here related to what I&#39;ve stated above, but I&#39;m not too sure that I want to get into some of these items just at this time. At least not in public. While I don&#39;t share these posts within my &lt;em&gt;close friend group&lt;/em&gt;, neither is this site exactly hidden. I think I&#39;ll just leave it at that for a bit. Talk about vague posting, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now for an attempt at something a little less depressing I guess. While I really, really have been enjoying Zettel Notes, I would like a way to more easily share pics on this site. Without the need to host the images myself. Yeah, that kinda limits me with workflow simplicity. I&#39;ve got the pixelfed account, so there is that, but then omg.lol also has a pretty simple image host as well. Both just take a little extra steps. But this should work, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.some.pics/swrogers/664a23faee93d.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cropped picture of my IronFlask coffee mug.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess that should do for today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Just another day</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/just-another-day/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-20T20:27:56+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/just-another-day/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;The 20th of the month, and the first time that I&#39;ve actually sat down at a computer to write a post in, oh, what seems like forever at this point. I&#39;ve remembered to &lt;code&gt;git pull --rebase&lt;/code&gt; so - hopefully - there won&#39;t be any errors thrown by git. What I&#39;ve not done is to come up with some kind of theme for todays entry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The morning was pretty much blown, not only was there no real sleep to have been had (stopped up nasal situation, creating a wonderfully sore throat), but then there was the need to get the two oldest and the youngest kiddos in for their annual &amp;quot;well child&amp;quot; check. Always a good time. At least our family doctor is easy to talk to and we generally really like her. Would definitely recommend her as a local doc anytime I see people ask about who to go to in any of the local groups. The only thing that I (we...) don&#39;t care so much for is the fact that her practice was sucked up into the local hospital conglomerate a handful of years ago. Ugh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;just-chillaxing-here&quot;&gt;Just chillaxing here &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#just-chillaxing-here&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I&#39;m just sitting here putting off one of the more dull parts of my duties. Instead of which, I&#39;m listening to my eldest twin talk his way through an attempted understanding of building a binary input system that outputs an analog number using simple logic gates. Not only has he basically taught this to himself (with a small amount of input from myself), but he has more or less sucessfully reversed engineered a simple prebuilt machine and added a third bit. Listening to him explain the process, and be super excited about his progress, is enough to make this geeky Dad very, very proud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve also been kind of halfway &lt;em&gt;futzing&lt;/em&gt; (that&#39;s a technical term there) around with creating a process to pull in a weeks worth of &lt;code&gt;raindrop.io&lt;/code&gt; links into distinct data directories within this blog. I&#39;ve got a pretty simple solution that will pull in the previous weeks worth of items, create any necessary &lt;code&gt;YYYY/MM&lt;/code&gt; directory, then write a &lt;code&gt;response.json&lt;/code&gt; file containing the items. I guess I&#39;d probably rather create &lt;em&gt;week number&lt;/em&gt; directories as opposed to month directories though - that would make more sense in that process. The idea being that I could have a weekly post of all the links that I wanted to save and share for that previous week. I also do use the paid &lt;a href=&quot;http://raindrop.io/&quot;&gt;raindrop.io&lt;/a&gt; account, so I think I could maybe link to the cache - not sure on that, though. At least for me, I could.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This past few days I&#39;ve also been trying to get more familier with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://nyxt.atlas.engineer/&quot;&gt;Nyxt&lt;/a&gt; web browser. It&#39;s kind of an &lt;em&gt;on again, off again&lt;/em&gt; deal with me. Some of my browsing I do over an X tunnel, and nyxt just seems a little bit faster than firefox. Plus, it&#39;s &lt;code&gt;lisp&lt;/code&gt; based and I&#39;m still in that phase of learning new things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, I think we shall call it an end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>End of an era</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/end-of-an-era/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-21T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/end-of-an-era/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Today was the recognition ceremony for our fifth grader. This is certainly a special class, one that we feel honored to have gotten to be involved with. Our fellow parents are amazing, our son&#39;s peer group is just flat out phenomenal, we couldn&#39;t ask for anything better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This class has marked a couple of milestones. First, the school principal started out with this group in kindergarten. She&#39;s been a wonderful person - an advocate above all who believes in all the students. Sadly for this school, she is leaving for another district.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second, our young man has had a gifted IEP for a number of years now (recall what I said about the principal being an advocate?), and he was the first gifted student for his particular gifted facilitator. She, too, has been a joy to work with. We have had nothing but positive memories for this school and the people there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, we still have one more kiddo to take through this journey. He is getting to go through this school&#39;s beginning of a Montessori program. So far, it&#39;s been good for him. We would have loved to have had more of them go through this type of learning system, but at least one is able to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we first moved here, I admit to having doubts about this area and this school - but no longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A somewhat productive day</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-somewhat-productive-day/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-22T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-somewhat-productive-day/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;If I were to be honest - and really why wouldn&#39;t I be so - today has been something of a productive day. I don&#39;t feel like I have a whole lot of &lt;em&gt;actual product&lt;/em&gt; that came out of today, but I do feel that I made some learning progress today for work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That, my friends, is certainly positive. I&#39;m learning some working details of our new ticketing/asset/configuration item/project system. We&#39;re moving from the atlassian product, so it&#39;s something along those lines. I don&#39;t mind jira, but it&#39;ll be nice to not have different login system and be able to use our single sign on. Plus, while I will be a department admin, I don&#39;t have to admin the whole thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today was also the last day of school for the kindergartner and the fifth grader. It&#39;s bittersweet all around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, it&#39;s a short update day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>One more day down</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/one-more-day-down/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-23T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/one-more-day-down/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;It&#39;s certainly been a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And night, honestly. Late last night our eldest came home with his little one. I will say that it wasn&#39;t entirely unexpected, and that we as a family are glad to have them here. We are grateful that we are &lt;em&gt;able&lt;/em&gt; to have them here. This weekend will be a bit of work, as I have kinda taken over the extra room and made an office out of it, which will have to be swapped back over to make room for the two of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve also got a couple of us in the home who aren&#39;t exactly feeling all that well. One probably should have come home early with an ear infection/headache/head cold. Myself, I&#39;m halfway stopped up with a scratchy throat and can&#39;t sleep worth a darn. It&#39;s been a pretty not so fun time overall here in the household.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The twins have the last day of school tomorrow, assuming that they are both able to go. Next year they will be finishing up middle school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now, I&#39;m just sitting here, listening to the quiet that is octonaughts. Who are also asking for peace and quiet. It&#39;s kinda meta.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>So so tired today</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/so-so-tired-today/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-24T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/so-so-tired-today/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;It&#39;s been a day of feeling absolutely miserable. Took a couple of benadryl may night, with the hope being that I might be able to some decent sleep to go along with being stopped up with a sore throat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, that didn&#39;t work too well. While I was basically falling asleep at 22:00 last night, I also managed to forget to put the recycling and trash out for the morning. At least I was able to get them out this morning. The problem with benadryl is that it takes forever to wear out of my system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So even right now, at 1700 the next day, I feel like I could go to bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least the grand daughter wasn&#39;t too bad today! She doesn&#39;t really know us, but we&#39;ve been working on that and I think that we are making progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, here&#39;s a photo I took of our backyard swing while I was pushing our six year old on it. Enjoy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.some.pics/swrogers/66510ce975b2b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Picture of green grass with an empty swing set seat hanging on the left side.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna read my other &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt; posts?&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
