<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="pretty-atom-feed.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Just Some Place</title>
  <subtitle>Just some place for me to write some things.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/" />
  <updated>2025-03-17T20:09:27Z</updated>
  <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Shane Rogers</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Some Stories</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/some-stories/" />
    <updated>2025-03-17T20:09:27Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/some-stories/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s been a slow week or so, not that that&#39;s a bad thing at all. Sometimes we just need to take a couple of days and not do anything at all. It&#39;s actually kind of nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The past couple of weekends had been nothing but &lt;em&gt;go go go&lt;/em&gt; and it can be just a bit draining on the psyche.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am back to the point of being maxxed out on my leave at work, so once again I get to take payday Friday&#39;s off. Which, I will admit, I have most assuradely gotten used to and most certainly look forward to! Now, if only I could somehow finagle a way to get every Friday off. That would be super nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We did manage to get out, either Friday or Saturday - I don&#39;t actually remember to be honest, to have dinner and a walk downtown. It was pretty good, nice and shockingly quiet. Well, as quiet as can ever be in downtown Lawrence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a couple of highlights - we found ourselves at a story book session, where people were telling there personal &amp;quot;ups and downs&amp;quot; of life. It did get me thinking, though, about getting words down on the screen of things that I have seen and experienced. While we might not think that our lives are very interesting (believe you me - mine is not) it&#39;s still not a bad idea to get the words down. If not for others, for yourself, possibly for your family. Of course, I can&#39;t say that I&#39;ve publicised to my family that this site exists, but I&#39;m not exactly difficult to find either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ll have to see what all I can come up with along that line. Growing up in an old mining town, in the middle of nowhere, I&#39;ve got some tales to tell and they may be interesting to some. Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end of the night we found our way to a bar and I found a band that actually interests me - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dustcityopera.com&quot;&gt;Dust City Opera&lt;/a&gt;. Eclectic for sure. I can&#39;t say that I&#39;ve heard a whole lot of kick ass bands that feature a trombone and clarinet. Certainly cool, and I very much liked them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 78/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>One More Birthday Season Down</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/one-more-birthday-season-down/" />
    <updated>2025-03-08T21:47:31Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/one-more-birthday-season-down/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some people have &lt;em&gt;Holiday Season&#39;s&lt;/em&gt;, well, we have &lt;em&gt;Birthday Season&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the span of a short handful of weeks, in some cases &lt;em&gt;days&lt;/em&gt;, we have four birthdays that we get to celebrate. Okay, sure, a pair of those are for a set of our twin kiddo&#39;s - but still, that&#39;s a couple of birthdays that still need to be seen to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s tough to know what to do for a teen birthday party. So what&#39;s the best thing to do? Ask them, of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One wanted a karaoke machine. Okay, that&#39;s easy enough and we&#39;ll count that as one gift in the bag. This one also doesn&#39;t really like cake - so they both decided that it would be awesome to have an ice cream social during their party, which isn&#39;t too difficult. Lot&#39;s of ice cream (and non-dairy as well) selection, with some toppings (you gotta have the caramel, hot fudge, chocolate, cherries, sprinkles and canned whipped cream stuff) make for a decent build-your-own-sundae. Plus, I do like to bake, so I threw in a couple trays of chocolate brownies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, let us not forget the 10 pizzas that needed to be ordered - gotta feed the teens lunch. Ha. And soda, lots of soda. And some water, you know, since it&#39;s good for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will admit that I was very anxious about this weekend and this party. It&#39;s the whole &amp;quot;well, I don&#39;t really have anything planned nor do I really know what to do for a bunch of junior high students during a birthday party.&amp;quot; I was worried that I didn&#39;t have enough brownies made (there were plenty). I was worried that there wouldn&#39;t be enough pizza (there was plenty). I was worried that nobody would have any fun (it seems that all enjoyed themselves).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t think there was anything to worry about. Everything seemed to go all right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, all said - I think next year we&#39;ll just do something like a Dave and Busters, or maybe something downtown if that&#39;s an option. I think it might be just as, um, &amp;quot;cheap&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 77/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Found the NAS, and moving day.</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/found-the-nas-and-moving-day/" />
    <updated>2025-03-02T14:35:16Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/found-the-nas-and-moving-day/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hey, I&#39;m now over 75 percent done with the current 100 Days To Offload challenge!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that that&#39;s out of the way... yesterday I almost thought that I had lost my Zimaboard NAS parts. I had recalled bringing the parts downstairs to look them over and get things put together. Only I needed to get an actual physical network connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I put them away until I could figure something out. In what I&#39;m sure I was thinking to be a really safe place at the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I was thinking, &amp;quot;Self, I haven&#39;t seen that Zima Cube thing in awhile, you should probably find that!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Evidently, I had placed it in about the safest place one could have done so: somewhere I had no idea where that might have been. Which was hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just before bed, I&#39;m standing in our room, looking at the bookshelf that I had put in a few months ago and already filled up. I see this short cardboard box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, to be fair I had seen and known this was there before. Thing is, I had thought that the box everything was in was larger. You know where this is going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medium story short, I found my Zima NAS parts! Along with the pair of 12TB (I think) drives that I got for it. Whew.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;moving-day&quot;&gt;Moving day&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, our oldest kiddo and his partner moved into a new apartment. We weren&#39;t able to help them as much as we would have liked to, due to missed communication, but at least we did get there in time to move some heavy arsed couch and dresser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Poor kid was limping pretty well when we got there, I&#39;m hoping he had a good night&#39;s sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were able to have them over to our house last night as well for dinner, which is always good. He had lived with us for, I think, about a year at this point. Maybe. We&#39;ll miss having him around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We did get them a, hopefully, nice coffeemaker and some mugs. Then, last night I was thinking that I&#39;d love to give them a bag of our coffee... Which must mean that I really, really love those kids. 😂&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah well, I think we&#39;re good for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until next I put fingers to keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 76/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A portrait of a chicken</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-portrait-of-a-chicken/" />
    <updated>2025-02-28T01:33:31Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-portrait-of-a-chicken/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A portrait of a &amp;quot;Chicken&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type=&quot;image/avif&quot; srcset=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-portrait-of-a-chicken/VrFUxupE-Y-3000.avif 3000w&quot;&gt;&lt;source type=&quot;image/webp&quot; srcset=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-portrait-of-a-chicken/VrFUxupE-Y-3000.webp 3000w&quot;&gt;&lt;img loading=&quot;lazy&quot; decoding=&quot;async&quot; src=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-portrait-of-a-chicken/VrFUxupE-Y-3000.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Photo of a gray and white sheepadoodle. She&#39;s laying on her bed, staring straight at the camera, her mouth slightly open in what looks like a smile. Her eyes are obscured by her long, scraggly hair.&quot; style=&quot;width:80%;height:80%;&quot; width=&quot;3000&quot; height=&quot;4000&quot;&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;The Sheepadoodle&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you know, you know. 😅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;....her name, it&#39;s Chicken.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Hey, it&#39;s a long weekend</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/hey-its-a-long-weekend/" />
    <updated>2025-02-27T23:29:34Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/hey-its-a-long-weekend/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ah, I am once again at the point to where my vacation time is maxed out at work. So it&#39;s either use &amp;quot;it or don&#39;t gain any more&amp;quot; time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing that I do really enjoy about my coworkers and my manager staff is that they absolutely, positively, expect and &lt;strong&gt;encourage&lt;/strong&gt; us to use our time. It is a nice change of pace from those souls who work for people who actively discourage such use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my position, we max out at 304 hours of vacation. I accumulate 8 hours every pay period (less two pay periods, where there are three paychecks in a month, I think...). We also accumulate 4 hours of sick leave every check, which does not max out - which is nice. I&#39;m near to 750 hours there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t take a whole lot of time off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I have kind of grown accustomed to having every other Friday off. It&#39;s pretty sweet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some other news, I&#39;ve been slowly trimming the dead nail off of my right thumb. There is just a small sliver left on the side at this point. I&#39;m just really glad that I haven&#39;t caught it on anything and ripped the thing out yet. I don&#39;t believe that would be too pleasant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t have much else going on right now. Oh, we did have the youngest kiddos birthday party last weekend, which had an excellent turn out! We paired up with a friend and rented out Up And Away Play for Sunday morning for a couple of hours. It went pretty well, though I&#39;m not sure we&#39;ll do the same next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next up we&#39;ll have the twins&#39; birthday party, which is set up for an ice cream social slash pizza party slash other stuff at a city community room. It should be fun. They&#39;ve been inviting a handful of friends, which for one of them is a little out of his comfort zone. Sort of. Although I will say, he had an excellent way to put things: &lt;em&gt;While I may have few people that I would count as friends, because I think there is a difference between friendship and those that I have positive interactions with&lt;/em&gt;. I was completely blown away by that when my wife told me that he&#39;d said that. It&#39;s just so mature, and I don&#39;t even think I&#39;d come up with that one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love my kids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 75/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Late long mid-week update</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/late-long-mid-week-update/" />
    <updated>2025-02-20T18:15:23Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/late-long-mid-week-update/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today is Thursday, February 20, in this, what has been yet another exceptionally long week in this year of 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The kiddos had school,  thus far, only one day this week due to insanely cold weather and snowy conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve had whatever illness run through our home over the last couple of weeks,  with the youngest finally getting over most of what he had yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This weekend is going to be good and busy as well. We&#39;ve got the youngest kiddo&#39;s bday party lined up at a really cool playplace in town, paired up with a friend whose kiddo shares a pretty close date as well - so we just rented the whole place for the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve got to look at getting a cake made too, for either his actual birthday or the same evening. He likes Minecraft,  so at least that should be easier than, oh, a Dalek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve got a handful - six - of old phones that need to be reset and packed up to send in for rebates. That&#39;ll be fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s all I&#39;ve got at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 74/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Yep, It&#39;s Gonna Be A Loss</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/yep-its-gonna-be-a-loss/" />
    <updated>2025-02-17T21:29:01Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/yep-its-gonna-be-a-loss/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As you most likely do not recall, back in middle December I decided to give my thumb a &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-day-of-firsts&quot;&gt;smashing good time in my car door&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It hurt quite a lot and after doing the drainage thing for a handful of days it started feeling much better and the healing process began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not that the healing process hadn&#39;t &lt;em&gt;technically&lt;/em&gt; began the instant it happened, but, yeah. Very nearly the entire undernail and nail bed bruised and it (still) kinda looked like I had painted that particular fingernail black.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hope was that I was not going to lose the nail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For awhile it sure seemed like I was in the clear on that one!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you probably might guess, it does appear that I&#39;ll be losing the nail. Not that it&#39;s anything major, just kinda some suckage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made the mistake of picking at the edge of the nail, which then more or less started the displacement of it all. The other day I was putting my jacket on, getting it zipped and cozy, and somehow - someway - caught the edge of my thumbnail in the cloth. Half the nailbed came out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had to do some trim work on it, will probably be doing trimwork on it for the next few weeks or so. Sleeping with a bandaid on it so I don&#39;t catch it on anything in my sleep and rip the bad boy out. That would suck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is certainly gnarly, and has been quite some time since this has happened to any of my nails. Our oldest has had the privilege of losing not &lt;em&gt;one&lt;/em&gt;, but &lt;em&gt;two&lt;/em&gt; nails in his short life thus far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 73/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>New phone setup day</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/new-phone-setup-day/" />
    <updated>2025-02-16T01:28:32Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/new-phone-setup-day/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Received the new phone yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve moved on from one provider,  T-MOBILE, to another,  ATT. Not really sure which is better at this point - they are basically all just a commodity now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My line was the last to arrive and the last to be ported, out of six I believe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything with the setup went okay, just trying to get the final number actually ported and the esim activated took about an hour on the phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, my wife probably spent about five hours on the phone with the ATT Costco support line. Way more than desired, and a lot more than we&#39;ve spent with support on T-MOBILE over the course of 18 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But. Now we should be good. Now we worry about having everything we need from the old phones before we wipe them and send them on their merry way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall though, I do kinda like the new device. I&#39;ve been a Google Pixel user and disciple since the OG XL, so it&#39;s a little different to be away and on the Samsung 25 Ultra train.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do like the stylus though, haven&#39;t had one of those since the Note 7. Which I did not have very long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 72/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Just a quick note</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/just-a-quick-note/" />
    <updated>2025-02-12T18:13:54Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/just-a-quick-note/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Still doing some final checks and balances on things around these parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I noticed that, for some reason, that old &amp;quot;holiday&amp;quot; post decided to show up in the feed and echofeed grabbed it as well. Not sure what that was about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do know that I had to redo the git repo, again, seeing as how Zettel Notes still had an older version and, with the merge settings I have, happily forced up the older branch. Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All right. Let&#39;s see how this one pops up!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A New Look</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-new-look/" />
    <updated>2025-02-12T16:14:03Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-new-look/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For those that might be paying attention you&#39;ll notice that I&#39;ve changed up the templating for the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those that follow this site in their RSS feeds (probably just me, honestly), I&#39;ll apologize for the spammage that was just sent your way. Fortunately it looks like it was only limited to the last 10 posts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve moved from the old &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/madrilene/eleventy-excellent&quot;&gt;eleventy-excellent&lt;/a&gt; fork that I had, to a design based around the standard &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/11ty/eleventy-base-blog&quot;&gt;eleventy base&lt;/a&gt; blog design - with a spritzing of &lt;a href=&quot;https://readable-css.freedomtowrite.org&quot;&gt;readable css&lt;/a&gt;. Trying to keep things simple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The home page is basically the &amp;quot;about me&amp;quot; page that seems to be the popular thing to do these days, along with the latest 5 posts and 5 links that I&#39;ll eventually populate. I don&#39;t know that I&#39;ll do a whole linkroll/linkblog/whatever, and I&#39;ll certainly not replace raindrop.io with this, but it&#39;s just yet another section for content and a place to save yet more things for me to lose track of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;d say this was a lot more difficult than it needed to be, but I think I was just overcomplicating the whole &amp;quot;multiple remotes&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;multiple branches&amp;quot; git thing. Still hosted on github pages, still in the same repo. Yippee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 71/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>