<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="pretty-atom-feed.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Just Some Place</title>
  <subtitle>Just some place for me to write some things.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/" />
  <updated>2025-04-30T17:03:06Z</updated>
  <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Shane Rogers</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Did you expect an update?</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/did-you-expect-an-update/" />
    <updated>2025-04-30T17:03:06Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/did-you-expect-an-update/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The title of this particular entry, &lt;em&gt;Did you expect an update?&lt;/em&gt;, is kind of a funny one to me because of some recent experiences that we&#39;ve been having with a certain vendor at work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with vendors and being at the mercy of their support system - or lack thereof in some cases - really kind of sucks sometimes. We&#39;ve got a handful of them that we have to deal with on a daily basis and some of them are certainly better than others. At least they are before they get bought up by an even larger suckier vendor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of our products is &lt;em&gt;SaaS&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;IaaS&lt;/em&gt; and all that jazz. It&#39;s great when it works, not so much when it doesn&#39;t. Naturally there aren&#39;t a whole lot of logging options on these things, so we kinda just have to roll with the punches on what can be done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This particular product has been having some intermittent, very challenging to replicate, user presentation issues. Not widespread, yet, but who the heck knows when that could happen. We decide to open up a support request. We send them the only logs that I can grab - stuff from tailing the systemd crud generated from their application we use as a bridge. These definitely show some communication issues. But again, only intermittently. Usually our people are able to wait and refresh and have things &amp;quot;fixed&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ll not go into the ordeal that ensued...but good grief it was weeks of back and forth. Eventually, after no updates from their end for quite some time (they had actually determined the problem to be a bug on their side, go figure), they patch one of our development instances. Of course, I was out when this happened and we were unable to respond and test for the last portion of that week. Then there is the weekend. Then I&#39;ve got a Monday to play catch up with everything else that happens. So I didn&#39;t get to check the status Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuesday I go to check on it. They&#39;ve closed the request. We were not stoked about that. Not even a &amp;quot;Hey, we&#39;re getting ready to close out your request&amp;quot; email. Remind, it&#39;s perfectly okay for &lt;em&gt;them&lt;/em&gt; to go a week or more with no contact. We fire off an email to our contact rep, then I call support. Fortunately it was not too challenging to get it re-opened. Just far too many hoops to jump through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that, we request that they send the patch to our main testing instance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Well, we&#39;ve just bundled that up into the next big overall patch that will be pushed so you&#39;ll get it then.&amp;quot; Fine. Just don&#39;t close the damn support ticket until after that, which doesn&#39;t happen for a week or so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guess what they attempted to do? I&#39;ll give you three guesses and the first two don&#39;t count.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At least this time I did receive an email letting me know that a solution had been offered. The hell it was, I think. We haven&#39;t even had the chance to &lt;strong&gt;test&lt;/strong&gt; the patch since it&#39;s not been patched at this point. FFS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, yeah. They kind of expect updates for absolutely no reason whatsoever. I&#39;m tempted to update the damn thing on the daily just for shits and giggles. I&#39;m not, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do imagine that for those of you out there who deal with vendor support probably have similar experiences. It is what it is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And yeah, I know that none of you actually expect an update from me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 86/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Some notes of the week?</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/some-notes-of-the-week/" />
    <updated>2025-04-25T16:11:41Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/some-notes-of-the-week/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So there are times that I think that, perhaps, I should just do week-style notes like some other people do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nah, I think that would be far too much pressure on me. Ha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I&#39;ll just continue to write on whatever sounds good at the time as a somewhat historical log of my life and times and whatever else is going on around me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last weekend we headed down to the Southeast part of the State where I grew up. I hail from Galena Kansas. It&#39;s an old mining town, lead infested, seriously poor. Honestly, about what one would expect from a predominately &amp;quot;red&amp;quot; state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s always challenging and difficult to go back there and I think that&#39;s why I don&#39;t make that pilgramage any more than every handful of years or so. I&#39;d love to be able to see my friends more often back that way, but we&#39;ve all got families and things going on to make our lives extremely busy which makes getting together tough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were able to at least meet up for some lunch at a little place called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.latinfusionjoplin.com/home&quot;&gt;Latin Fusion&lt;/a&gt; that was pretty good. Talked about work and kids and geek stuff for a couple of hours - it was a good time to do some catch up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course we did spend a little time at my Dad&#39;s place. The whole reason for heading down that way was for the grandkids to meet granddad. While it would be nice to spend more time with him, my Dad is kind of set in his ways (to put it kindly). We don&#39;t always see eye to eye on some things, so we try not to broach certain subjects. I&#39;ll leave it as an exercise to the reader to figure out what those might actually be. When some of those ideas did start to come up - it was time to get ready to head out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, by that time, it really was about time to hit the road for the three hour trip if we wanted to miss traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the way down we took the Missouri side. We came back to Lawrence on the Kansas side. I had wanted to show my family some of the other areas that I grew up, so that was the perfect opportunity. We drove through mainstreet Galena, not much to see there, but it does actually look nicer than it used to. Still a dieing town though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then it was through the old neighborhood in Riverton where the early years of my life were spent. That old place is...there really are no words for how run down that old home is. Growing up we had a chainlink fence, at some point it was replaced with a wooden fence. Which has never, ever, been maintained. One Christmas we got a Douglas Fir that was decorated and used as our tree, afterwards we planted it just outside my bedroom window. It was super cool to me, but was removed by somebody who purchased the home after we moved. I hate to see the disrepair of the place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the bright side, I picked up a physical copy of the &lt;em&gt;Lunar Remastered&lt;/em&gt; edition on Xbox. I&#39;ve got copies of them (Lunar and Lunar 2 - Eternal Blue) on Sega CD. Too bad I no longer have my Sega CD. Or Genesis. Or 32X. Or Super Nintendo. Or Neo Geo AES (2 joystick edition). I could cry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Needless to say I&#39;ve also added the remastered version to my Steam Wishlist and will pick up another copy of it when a sale hits. Because reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why can&#39;t I save money again?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 85/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Weekend To Come</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-weekend-to-come/" />
    <updated>2025-04-16T15:27:41Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-weekend-to-come/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;To say that I have not really been in a writing mood would probably be a large understatement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, that sentence pretty much sums up the way I&#39;ve been feeling over the past few weeks. Writing, reading, pretty much doing anything - I don&#39;t know if it&#39;s just the time of year or what, but good grief have I just been in something of a &lt;em&gt;meh&lt;/em&gt; type mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our past few weekends have felt like they&#39;ve been non-stop, with hardly any time to rest or recoup and I don&#39;t anticipate things slowing down any at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This weekend, beginning Friday afternoon, we will be taking off to head to the Southeast part of the State. I&#39;ve not been back home in a couple of years at this point and we kind of need to get visiting some people. Mainly my Dad. He is getting up there in age and has not actually seen his youngest grandkid (who is 7...yeah, I&#39;m a bad kid I guess), nor is he super mobile which makes it difficult for him to get up this way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s only about 3 hours, but it&#39;s also about a generation away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Dad and I basically get along all right, but there are certain things that we just more or less have to agree to disagree on - and that is okay. Politics, mainly. I just kind of leave it at that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hope had been to be able to meet up with some old friends of mine as well, but from the sound of things they&#39;ve had what was to be an empty weekend suddenly sprout full of stuff to do. That happens, and I totally get it - especially with larger families and teenagers and active kids. We are going to try to at least grab lunch on Saturday, so we shall see how that goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was last down that way a couple of years ago...I don&#39;t recall the exact reason for going, besides it having been about a decade prior before that. It was the first time that I&#39;d been back to my old home since before the Joplin tornado. I may not have lived through that, but having family and friends be in the area and experiencing what that was...heart wrenching. Things had definitely changed and I didn&#39;t even recognize some of the old stomping grounds of mine. The only way that I could describe it was &amp;quot;surreal&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last time, I had hoped to be able to bring back a few things of mine from my childhood. Silly things like game systems and models. Yeah, that didn&#39;t happen. They weren&#39;t tossed, but with a home move and storage not ideal who knows what became of all that stuff. Ah well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am looking forward to going, it will be good to have the kiddo&#39;s down there with me this time - I&#39;m just hoping that they aren&#39;t bored out of their minds. Which, I know they will be. There just isn&#39;t much to do in an old mining town that&#39;s (while it&#39;s doing better than it was) on its last legs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 84/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Kite That Almost Escaped</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-kite-that-almost-escaped/" />
    <updated>2025-04-06T21:26:55Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-kite-that-almost-escaped/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Growing up, I always loved kite flying season. Not only did it mean that Spring was here, but that Summer was (as Frog would say) just around the corner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Living just across the street from a cornfield did have its benefits. One of which being that it provided for a most excellent place to go outside and fly a kite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My friends and I would make judicious use of that field for our kiting excursions - and living in the Midwest provided for plenty of windy days and many opportunities to get lots and lots of elevation for our kites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember one such day, my friend and I were out using a brand new kite he had just picked up. It was your standard delta wing style, I don&#39;t remember what design was on it, but that is immaterial at this point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The string we were using was a ginormous spool of some style of sewing or crocheting thread. Thankfully a very strong string, and ridiculously long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wind that day was not vicious, but still a really gusty wind. More than enough to have our kite flying pretty high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recall that for some reason my friend had to head inside and had asked that I keep a hold of the kite. You can probably guess where this is heading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A handful of minutes pass, I&#39;m still letting some string out so the kite can soar higher and higher....when suddenly the spool rips out of my hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, these types of spools aren&#39;t really meant for what we are using them for. They kinda flip flop around and are more for - you know - craft type stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There I am, entrusted with my best friends&#39; kite, which has now literally flown away from me. I&#39;m like, &amp;quot;oh crap!&amp;quot;. Panic sets in, I take off after the spool, which is being drug along the ground. I almost grab it a couple of times, only to have the thing slip from my not-nearly-strong-enough grasp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this time I&#39;m nearly in tears, thinking that I&#39;m going to have to tell my best friend in the whole world that I&#39;ve let his kite get away from me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember now that we are in a cornfield. Thankfully this field is not currently planted, plus, there are a number of sections that have old - very sturdy - stalk sections and other items that might just possibly be able to snag a line of string.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which is exactly what happens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will never forget my feeling that day, when I was finally able to get that kite brought back under control. Winding that spool back up was certainly a challenge, but I was gracious to have the wing back on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more I think about it, I don&#39;t believe we ever flew kites again after that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 83/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A Little, A Lot</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-little-a-lot/" />
    <updated>2025-04-01T22:32:55Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/a-little-a-lot/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The end of last week was the end of an era for our household.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday was the final middle school play performance for our twins, as they are nearing the end of junior high school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ll admit to being an extremely proud parent of those two. That&#39;s not too say that I&#39;m not proud of the other three kids we&#39;ve got, heck I&#39;m proud of each and every one of them. But it&#39;s beyond heartwarming, in that it&#39;s something one has a very difficult time to put properly into words. I am not too proud to admit to having very nearly come to tears at times watching these performances: be they plays, musicals, or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is bittersweet, though, in that the final play for middle school was not one in which they were able to have larger, more prominent, parts in. However, the roles were very much important to be had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The play: &lt;em&gt;Little Women&lt;/em&gt;. The roles: Professor Bhaer and Mr. Laurence. Both very respectable, and they did fantastic jobs. As an extra bonus the teacher/director is such an amazing and awesome person, who loves all of the kids also really loves our youngest kiddo and does her best to work him into the performances as well - thus we&#39;ve got photos of all three on stage. Super proud parent moment, that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can tell, I&#39;m one grateful, proud Dad. Quite a lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I cannot wait to see them on bigger stages and bigger productions to see what they are capable of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 82/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Yard Swimming</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/yard-swimming/" />
    <updated>2025-03-28T16:02:38Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/yard-swimming/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I hear you saying &amp;quot;that&#39;s a strange title for a post.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is, isn&#39;t it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It might make sense here in a couple of minutes, if you&#39;ll just give me a bit of time to get the words down on bits and bytes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be doing a bit of jumping around time for my childhood slash &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/growingup&quot;&gt;growing up&lt;/a&gt; posts, really it all just kind of depends on what pops into my head at certain times. Along with whatever memories I can manage to actually keep track of throughout the course of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s not easy, sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Growing up in a small, unincorporated town in South East Kansas did come with some good times for me. Believe it or not. We lived in Riverton, which as its namesake is actually alongside a river. We had a coal burning electric plant (long since shut down), a pretty decent school, a small post post office, and the &lt;em&gt;World Famous Spring River Inn&lt;/em&gt;. Whether or not it was actually &lt;em&gt;world famous&lt;/em&gt; is, of course, up for debate. They did have some damn good homemade cinnamon rolls though - those things were &lt;strong&gt;ginormous&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I had indicated in a previous post, we lived on a corner lot in a relatively small, moderately friendly neighborhood. I had a couple of friends that lived across the street and would spend a lot of time over at thier home, playing with whatever was available at the time. They had a pretty large side yard and back yard - complete with woods and a large corn field. I&#39;ll have some stories about that corn field later, but not today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One feature of our neighborhood was that the interior lots (of which our house was on one) had really large ditches on the edge of the property. Another feature is that, since our town was situated on a river, the land had a tendency towards being water logged and easily flooded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You could probably extrapolate at least partly where this is going now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One year we had quite the torrential rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was one home in the neighborhood, on the other end from our home, who had an exceptionally large section of yard next to their house. It was also quite depressed from the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, fortunately for this homeowner, from what I recall it was only the yard itself that was pretty low and the actual house was elevated enough to prevent any water damage. There definitely could have been the opportunity for flood damage, here, because the entire side yard was basically turned into a small lake for us neighborhood kids to frolic around in for a day or so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And frolic we did! I don&#39;t remember how many of us there were, probably 10 or more, but it was a great distraction from whatever was going on during those times. There was a storm tube that was beneath the road, and I remember us riding our bikes off that sucker and tumbling off into the water. It was a good time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t know how many kids I watched bike off that, to be flipped over their handlebars because the lip of the metal storm tube was bent up. Even I had to experience that one, for some reason or other. It was fun, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I drove back through there decades later. It didn&#39;t look nearly as large as memory served, but that doesn&#39;t change the experience we had. The memories will remain, and the memories will always be fond for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 81/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Two calls and two tales</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/two-calls-and-two-tales/" />
    <updated>2025-03-23T17:41:50Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/two-calls-and-two-tales/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My Dad called me yesterday afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He, and the rest of my family are basically the only people that I would even consider answering the phone for. Everybody else can leave a message and maybe I&#39;ll carve some time out of my life to call you back. But I wouldn&#39;t count on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He (my Dad) has actually called my twice now within the last few weeks. He&#39;s getting up there in age and it&#39;s been awhile since I&#39;ve made the approximately four hour trek south to see him. I&#39;m also really bad at calling him. Sometimes I don&#39;t think I&#39;ve been a great son.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would make the &amp;quot;politics&amp;quot; excuse, but I don&#39;t talk politics with my Dad. I do love my Dad and we did used to be pretty close, but we&#39;ve grown apart. As happens with some people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyhow. Yesterday he calls and of course I answer. His question is an interesting one: &amp;quot;I bought this 60 plus inch Roku TV, if I plug it in do I need the internet in order to stream or whatever it&#39;s called?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me qualify something here for you, dear reader: my Dad still has to use a flip phone, is absolutely computer and technology illiterate and has really no desire to learn. Which is fine. He&#39;s done all right with what he&#39;s got thus far and has no need to complicate his life any more than necessary. At least he can text message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting back to the story, I say: &amp;quot;yeah, you would need the internet to properly use your Roku TV. Do you even have the internet?&amp;quot; Of course he does not. But, he can have it installed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excellent. Next, he wants to know if I could help him get things sorted out over the phone. Yeah, no. I&#39;m not gonna go that route. I love you, Dad, but that&#39;s just not something that I&#39;m willing to invest my time and effort into. Far too frustrating. Well, could the installer help me, he asks. I guess that depends on the installer and the kind of day they&#39;ve had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s a tough call. I did let him know that we&#39;re planning on a visit soon - we actually just booked the hotel this morning - and that I could help him then. Until then, well, he&#39;s got a great new TV he can still use his satellite with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He&#39;s frustrated because he&#39;s paying all this money for DirecTV and really all he needs is.... Yeah. No comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We finished our conversation with a couple of tales about some former friends he&#39;s had, both of which kind of relate to feeling like time party of which is being taken for granted. That thought just kind of popped into my head now and the more I think about, the truer it is. My Dad, love him, sometimes needs to know how to say &amp;quot;no&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From one individual who keeps using him as the one and only emergency contact, who does and does not want help even when her health and well being are at risk, to the old friend who&#39;s gone blind and literally cannot see that the one person who has been there to take him to appointments and out for errands and beers and whatever else... My Dad&#39;s been pretty giving. It&#39;s tough to sit there and listen to someone complain about not having anyone that cares, when there is someone right next to you who does.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you&#39;re just done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He can be really, really good at cutting you off - but it&#39;s tough to do that for people that you care for and have been friends with for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t know where I was going, necessary, with this rambling story. But I figure it&#39;s yet more of my life to get out there. It&#39;s part of what makes me, me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 80/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>It&#39;s a start - Growing up</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/its-a-start-growing-up/" />
    <updated>2025-03-20T23:44:36Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/its-a-start-growing-up/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In my last post, I&#39;d said something about wanting to write more about myself. I think it had something to do with listening to a handful of random strangers talk about some of their stories and thinking that, while I may not have something that&#39;s directly relatable to the theme, I might have something that could be told.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doesn&#39;t everybody?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Theoretically, I should suppose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a &amp;quot;cusper&amp;quot;. A child of the (extremely) late seventies and (moreso) early eighties. I could prefix those with &amp;quot;nineteen-&amp;quot;, but just the thought of that makes me feel strange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While there was the existence of something that would become the Internet while I was growing up, I would never personally encounter the online world until well into high school. Personal computers were not a thing that every household had. Phones were hard wired to a wall and some even had rotary dials on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people had remote controls for their televisions. Those were called &amp;quot;kids&amp;quot;. We did actually eventually have a television with a remote, it was kinda cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I grew up in a really cool time. We spent a lot of time outside playing. A lot of time with friends. I don&#39;t dislike my childhood, but I do think it was a unique time in history. I&#39;m glad that I am not maturing during the current timeframe. I witnessed the growth of technology. For better or for worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My childhood was split between a small, unincorporated town and an old lead infested mining town. I think I have memories when we moved into the home that my parents purchased, but memory is a fuzzy thing. A small three bedroom, one bath ranch style home, situated on a corner section of what everyone fondly referred to as &amp;quot;the block.&amp;quot; More of an oblong rectangle, less of a square block.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had what seemed like a fairly large large, complete with chain link fence.  The majority of the homes in the neighborhood were similar, though they weren&#39;t actually the cookie cutter style of today&#39;s prefabricated HOA locales. The thought that some homes could even have more than one toilet, or heck even an complete extra bathroom, had never ever entered my thoughts. We just made do. Which isn&#39;t too difficult when you&#39;re only a family of three.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, we didn&#39;t live there very long. At least, not as a whole family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My parents say, even to this day, that they love each other. That&#39;s hard to believe. They were divorced by the time I was in fifth or sixth grade. Fifth I think. By then, I was in the custody of my father and we were in another town.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new school, different friends, more to tell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For later. Plus, more backstory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 79/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Some Stories</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/some-stories/" />
    <updated>2025-03-17T20:09:27Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/some-stories/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s been a slow week or so, not that that&#39;s a bad thing at all. Sometimes we just need to take a couple of days and not do anything at all. It&#39;s actually kind of nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The past couple of weekends had been nothing but &lt;em&gt;go go go&lt;/em&gt; and it can be just a bit draining on the psyche.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am back to the point of being maxxed out on my leave at work, so once again I get to take payday Friday&#39;s off. Which, I will admit, I have most assuradely gotten used to and most certainly look forward to! Now, if only I could somehow finagle a way to get every Friday off. That would be super nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We did manage to get out, either Friday or Saturday - I don&#39;t actually remember to be honest, to have dinner and a walk downtown. It was pretty good, nice and shockingly quiet. Well, as quiet as can ever be in downtown Lawrence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a couple of highlights - we found ourselves at a story book session, where people were telling there personal &amp;quot;ups and downs&amp;quot; of life. It did get me thinking, though, about getting words down on the screen of things that I have seen and experienced. While we might not think that our lives are very interesting (believe you me - mine is not) it&#39;s still not a bad idea to get the words down. If not for others, for yourself, possibly for your family. Of course, I can&#39;t say that I&#39;ve publicised to my family that this site exists, but I&#39;m not exactly difficult to find either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ll have to see what all I can come up with along that line. Growing up in an old mining town, in the middle of nowhere, I&#39;ve got some tales to tell and they may be interesting to some. Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end of the night we found our way to a bar and I found a band that actually interests me - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dustcityopera.com&quot;&gt;Dust City Opera&lt;/a&gt;. Eclectic for sure. I can&#39;t say that I&#39;ve heard a whole lot of kick ass bands that feature a trombone and clarinet. Certainly cool, and I very much liked them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 78/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>One More Birthday Season Down</title>
    <link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/one-more-birthday-season-down/" />
    <updated>2025-03-08T21:47:31Z</updated>
    <id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/one-more-birthday-season-down/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some people have &lt;em&gt;Holiday Season&#39;s&lt;/em&gt;, well, we have &lt;em&gt;Birthday Season&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the span of a short handful of weeks, in some cases &lt;em&gt;days&lt;/em&gt;, we have four birthdays that we get to celebrate. Okay, sure, a pair of those are for a set of our twin kiddo&#39;s - but still, that&#39;s a couple of birthdays that still need to be seen to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s tough to know what to do for a teen birthday party. So what&#39;s the best thing to do? Ask them, of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One wanted a karaoke machine. Okay, that&#39;s easy enough and we&#39;ll count that as one gift in the bag. This one also doesn&#39;t really like cake - so they both decided that it would be awesome to have an ice cream social during their party, which isn&#39;t too difficult. Lot&#39;s of ice cream (and non-dairy as well) selection, with some toppings (you gotta have the caramel, hot fudge, chocolate, cherries, sprinkles and canned whipped cream stuff) make for a decent build-your-own-sundae. Plus, I do like to bake, so I threw in a couple trays of chocolate brownies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, let us not forget the 10 pizzas that needed to be ordered - gotta feed the teens lunch. Ha. And soda, lots of soda. And some water, you know, since it&#39;s good for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will admit that I was very anxious about this weekend and this party. It&#39;s the whole &amp;quot;well, I don&#39;t really have anything planned nor do I really know what to do for a bunch of junior high students during a birthday party.&amp;quot; I was worried that I didn&#39;t have enough brownies made (there were plenty). I was worried that there wouldn&#39;t be enough pizza (there was plenty). I was worried that nobody would have any fun (it seems that all enjoyed themselves).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t think there was anything to worry about. Everything seemed to go all right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, all said - I think next year we&#39;ll just do something like a Dave and Busters, or maybe something downtown if that&#39;s an option. I think it might be just as, um, &amp;quot;cheap&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 77/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>