<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>My Corner of the Internet Feed for linkdump</title>
	<subtitle>Just my little corner of the internet.</subtitle>
	
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/"/>
	<updated>2025-02-11T04:27:31+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://shanewrogers.lol</id>
	<author>
		<name>Shane Rogers</name>
		<email>swrogers@omg.lol</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>What have I been doing</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/what-have-i-been-doing/"/>
		<updated>2024-11-17T15:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/what-have-i-been-doing/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;What have I been doing lately?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not much, I would say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did start a new book recently, &lt;em&gt;What Moves the Dead&lt;/em&gt; by &lt;em&gt;T Kingfisher&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe title=&quot;Pixelfed Post Embed&quot; src=&quot;https://pixelfed.social/p/swrogers/762107973477551400/embed?caption=false&amp;likes=false&amp;layout=compact&quot; class=&quot;pixelfed__embed&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%; border: 0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;allowfullscreen&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; defer=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://pixelfed.social/embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s a retelling of Poe&#39;s &lt;em&gt;Fall of the House of Usher&lt;/em&gt;. I&#39;m only a few chapters in, and it&#39;s fairly short, but so far it&#39;s pretty good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m still also reading The Expanse series as well, plus I&#39;ve picked up a decent number of other titles that will get added to the &lt;em&gt;to be read&lt;/em&gt; pile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I&#39;m preparing for the times when physical books are not as easily accessible, what with the way things are going. Both societally and politically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyhow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve also ordered a couple of 12TB hard drives to pair with my Zima Board NAS kit and am certainly looking forward to getting that set up to store my media on. The stack of Blu-ray movies and DVDs in our library are in desperate need of being ripped.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can&#39;t say that I&#39;m looking forward to that process, but it&#39;s needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another item that has had me occupied over the last couple of weeks or so is coming up with a new emacs config.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I have been using Doom Emacs for quite awhile at this point, I do like to know how things work a bit better, and this is a good way to grasp that understanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sad thing is, that I&#39;m afraid I will basically just wind up reimplementing Soon Emacs, only with elpaca.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of good things with Doom, however, so I may just stick it out with that. There are also some quirkiness&#39; as well - such as needing both &lt;em&gt;package!&lt;/em&gt; along with &lt;em&gt;use-package!&lt;/em&gt; to get something both installed and configured. It does make sense, seeing as &lt;em&gt;use-package!&lt;/em&gt; is not a package installer though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;sunday-linkdump&quot;&gt;Sunday Linkdump &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#sunday-linkdump&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://write.as/batata/observation&quot;&gt;https://write.as/batata/observation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Whoa, somebody who actually has more tabs opened up on their mobile browser than I do: 4500 to about 1600. I need to step up my game I guess! This is a great write up about setting up bookmark and RSS aggregation on their self hosted NAS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://about.iftas.org/2024/10/29/5-ways-to-fight-election-disinformation-on-bluesky-and-the-fediverse/&quot;&gt;https://about.iftas.org/2024/10/29/5-ways-to-fight-election-disinformation-on-bluesky-and-the-fediverse/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
From the &lt;em&gt;Federated Trust and Safety&lt;/em&gt; group, they&#39;ve got some great tips on fighting disinformation (aka baldfaced lies) in this new day and age. Timeless stuff, really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tunemymusic.com/transfer&quot;&gt;https://www.tunemymusic.com/transfer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Very handy little online tool for moving music playlists from service to service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, I believe we&#39;ll call it a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 52/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Not really reflection</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-really-reflection/"/>
		<updated>2024-11-10T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-really-reflection/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;I have just not really been feeling it over the last week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do believe that I shall leave it to as an exercise for the reader to figure out why that might be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Friday was my &amp;quot;off work&amp;quot; Friday, so it&#39;s essentially a four day weekend for me, what with tomorrow being Veteran&#39;s Day. I guess I won&#39;t actually complain about that, since there really are worse things going on right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, my complaints won&#39;t even be referable as &lt;em&gt;first world problems&lt;/em&gt;, for, you know, reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just don&#39;t understand some people&#39;s children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, I sure do believe that we&#39;re gonna waltz right into the &lt;em&gt;find out&lt;/em&gt; portion of the night&#39;s program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I, absolutely, one hundred percent, hope those people find the.... Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rather unfortunate aspect of all of this being, that those of us who do understand some of these things will also get to go along with this ride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t know who to blame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t know, I didn&#39;t understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I do know, is that I am at least fortunate being what I &lt;em&gt;am&lt;/em&gt;. A white, hetero male.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I&#39;m lucky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m also glad that I&#39;ve already got a mortgage and a roof over our heads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just want my family and kiddos and friends to be able to live and work and play in a safe world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m not too sure that&#39;s going to be the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;linkdump&quot;&gt;Linkdump &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#linkdump&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Molly White&#39;s Blogroll&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mollywhite.net/blogroll/&quot;&gt;https://www.mollywhite.net/blogroll/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If you&#39;re on the lookout for some good sources to fill out your feeds, here is a great start!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;John Scalzi  &lt;a href=&quot;https://whatever.scalzi.com/2024/11/09/making-money-in-the-next-four-years-and-why-you-need-to-plan-now-to-support-your-favorite-creators/&quot;&gt;https://whatever.scalzi.com/2024/11/09/making-money-in-the-next-four-years-and-why-you-need-to-plan-now-to-support-your-favorite-creators/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Another great read from a pretty good writer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scholar’s new rap album seeks to turn the tables on the ‘masters’ from the Old South&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/scholars-new-rap-album-seeks-to-turn-the-tables-on-the-masters-from-the-old-south-241895&quot;&gt;https://theconversation.com/scholars-new-rap-album-seeks-to-turn-the-tables-on-the-masters-from-the-old-south-241895&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Just seems extraordinarily interesting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 51/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Week that was and other stuff</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/week-that-was-and-other-stuff/"/>
		<updated>2024-10-14T14:50:30+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/week-that-was-and-other-stuff/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Time to play a little bit of catch-up, seeing as I didn&#39;t post anything yesterday. Or the day before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I shall wait for the collective &amp;quot;aww, shucks, we sure missed reading your stuff!&amp;quot;, because, yeah, it&#39;s still basically just for myself. Which is totally cool with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;last-week&quot;&gt;Last Week &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#last-week&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not a whole heck of a lot going on last week really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picked up the new work laptop so I could replace the one that has basically had the battery and keyboard crap all over itself, so that&#39;s been fun. Which, I&#39;m pretty sure that nobody in the history of the world has ever actually said. While I do have backups of everything and don&#39;t have much to worry about in that department, getting the new machine all sorted out is just a huge pain in the rear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, it is a great time to look and reflect on the applications that I &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; need to do my work with. Plus, it&#39;s been great to get away from Firefox and move my work browsing over to Vivaldi. So there is that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was able to get WSL2 set up, even exported/imported my old setup image which is amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We might finally have the Halloween costume situation sorted out for everyone in the house - no small feet these days. Yesterday we made a short trip to one of the regional &lt;em&gt;Spririt Halloween&lt;/em&gt; stores, conveniently located near a &lt;em&gt;Costco&lt;/em&gt; that we also needed to run into, to gather ideas and make a handful of purchases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the twins picked up some black raven stuff, about all that we needed to get afterwards was a black overcoat and now some black pants that he won&#39;t complain about. Wish us luck there. The overcoat was not very easy to find and we wound up spending a bit more than I&#39;d like - but, we sure do love our kids, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other twin was going to go with a Knight theme, but decided last minute not to go that route. Now he&#39;s going with an anime character. We had to order his costume last night, and the hope now is that it &lt;em&gt;fits him&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;isn&#39;t made super cheaply&lt;/em&gt;. So, we&#39;ll see there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wife picked up some cool face masks, the favorite at the moment would seem to be a broken doll. I really like the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For myself, I procured a &lt;em&gt;Phantom of the Opera&lt;/em&gt; style mask that I&#39;m hoping is able to complement the rest of the outfit that I&#39;ve got. I&#39;m not doing a silly cape, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The little one already had his costume purchased - an &lt;em&gt;Ender Dragon&lt;/em&gt; from &lt;em&gt;Minecraft&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next to youngest (but quite possibly the most mature) of the group, still has yet to really put a finger on what he&#39;ll do. We had thought that he and a friend were gonna do some kind of matching costume set, but that seems to have changed. Last year they did &lt;em&gt;Mario and Luigi&lt;/em&gt;, the year before was the &lt;em&gt;Sun and Moon&lt;/em&gt;. I don&#39;t know what they&#39;ll do yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do believe that was basically most of last week (with some smattering of yesterday, alas) which brings us to...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;this-week&quot;&gt;This Week &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#this-week&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s a short school week, which is always fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parent teacher conferences are at the end of this week. We&#39;ve really only got one kiddo who I&#39;m concerned about, but really, all in all I can&#39;t complain about our kids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The youngest kiddo has Fall Picture Day coming up Tuesday. Which at least kinda makes sense, moreso than the middle school who does picture day on like the third day of school. I, for one, am looking forward to when picture day happens like the week before school starts. It&#39;s only a matter of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve got some other appointments happening this week too, which shouldn&#39;t be too trying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the work front, I&#39;ll be taking part in a demo/question/answer session for some new tools that I&#39;m also in the middle of learning. Fun times, that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are also still fighting with getting things paid, so that blows chunks all over the road. Sometimes one wonders if the &lt;em&gt;right hand&lt;/em&gt; is aware that the &lt;em&gt;left hand&lt;/em&gt; exists and is doing things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;link-dump&quot;&gt;Link Dump &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#link-dump&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I might even have some links to dump on the post this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://htmlforpeople.com/&quot;&gt;HTML for people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I have yet to go through much of this, well, any of it really. But you can&#39;t go wrong with a good up to date source for learning HTML. From Blake Watson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-10-11/were-fighting-that-throwaway-culture-local-kitchenaid-repair-shop-gains-international-following&quot;&gt;A KitchenAid repair shop in Kansas found a global following by ‘fighting that throwaway culture’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Thought this was pretty cool, given that it&#39;s from the home State.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://every.to/p/the-disappearance-of-an-internet-domain&quot;&gt;The Disappearance of an Internet Domain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I have seen a lot of talk about this, given recent politcal happenings. This might be something to keep an eye on. I don&#39;t have any dot-io domains, but I do use some dot-io services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/parenting/article/we-only-learnt-of-our-sons-secret-online-life-after-he-died-at-20-rj3bqfnqn&quot;&gt;We only learnt of our son’s secret online life after he died at 25&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I&#39;ll admit, this one got me in the feels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that, we&#39;ll call it a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 46/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Call it a weekly wrapup</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/call-it-a-weekly-wrapup/"/>
		<updated>2024-09-08T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/call-it-a-weekly-wrapup/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Not much of an interesting week, this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been meaning to try to get something down and posted but it&#39;s been a week of zero motivation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven&#39;t even mowed the lawn in two weekends at this point. Fortunately I don&#39;t think I &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; to mow yet, but I probably will before the season is out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the twins was able to participate in the first cross country event this season and he did pretty well! I would like to be able to run with him, but I&#39;m not there yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still try to take my lunch hour excursions and walk. Generally I can get in just under three miles in about forty minutes. Then a quick shower before logging back in to work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My goal still remains to run a 5K. I&#39;m sure I&#39;ll get there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had ordered the &lt;em&gt;Run Your Own Mail Server&lt;/em&gt; book, by Michael W Lewis, towards the end of the pre-order period and it finally arrived this week! I&#39;ve run mail servers for myself in the past, generally through systems like &lt;a href=&quot;https://mailinabox.email/&quot;&gt;mail on a box&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://yunohost.org/&quot;&gt;yunonost&lt;/a&gt;. I think even at one point I had set up &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.qmailtoaster.net/&quot;&gt;qmail toaster&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it&#39;s nice to know more about the what&#39;s and the why&#39;s, and it looks like this most excellent book is going to help out in that department. I don&#39;t know that I&#39;ll set something up from scratch... But that is certainly an itch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.some.pics/swrogers/66de154608ac5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The book: Run Your Own Mail Server, by Michael W Lucas&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;linkdump&quot;&gt;Linkdump &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#linkdump&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sigops.org/2024/the-moral-implications-of-being-a-moderately-successful-computer-scientist-and-a-woman/&quot;&gt;The Moral Implications of Being a Moderately Successful Computer Scientist and a Woman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I have not read this one yet, but it&#39;s certainly high on my list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cleoinvestigation.notion.site/Investigating-Cleo-0796ef7ce8464a90ba388cdb68e08eef&quot;&gt;Investigating Cleo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
It&#39;s always entertaining to read about who mysterious anonymous posters might be, even if there is no real need or desire to dox anyone. I haven&#39;t made it through everything in this, but it&#39;s about a user in one of the math boards who always manages to post responses to some very challenging integration problems. Are they a team? Are they using multiple accounts? Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://earthly.dev/blog/golang-http/&quot;&gt;Building a Golang JSON HTTP Server - Earthly Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I&#39;ve been looking more into learning go, so it&#39;s nice to have more stuff to learn from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s all I&#39;ve got for now, until time the next all!&lt;br&gt;
This is post 36/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Long weekend and no motivation</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/long-weekend-and-no-motivation/"/>
		<updated>2024-09-02T16:00:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/long-weekend-and-no-motivation/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Happy long weekend all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can&#39;t really relax, I have this constant feeling today that I need to be doing something. Anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s not like I&#39;ve been lazy today, either. Woke up, made my mug of coffee. Cleaned out the floor of our &amp;quot;soon to be coat&amp;quot; closet. Emptied the dishwasher. Filled the dishwasher. Ran the dishwasher. Took my first sip of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still there are so many things that need to be done. Or, that I feel should be done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I should mow the lawn, for example.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can&#39;t get motivated today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-weekend&quot;&gt;The weekend &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#the-weekend&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had a pretty decent weekend I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saturday was a birthday party for the daughter of a friend. Our little man enjoys going over there, so it was a good time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunday was the penultimate day for the local water park to be open this year, so we went out that direction. I didn&#39;t go there as I&#39;m not as big a fan, but the wife and the little did go and seemed to enjoy the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Myself and the eldest twin went to the amusement park side. It was really pretty good, not too hot, not too many people. We were able to get in half a dozen rides in - mostly coasters - within a handful of hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any time you don&#39;t have to spend three hours in a single line is a good day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we met up and had dinner in the the amusement park so the little guy could ride some stuff too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then the adults got to eat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a successful trip, all in all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ll be back in a couple of weeks for the halloween haunts they set up. Those are great!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;link-dump&quot;&gt;Link dump &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#link-dump&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A day late and a dollar short. Refunds can be had at the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fighthealthinsurance.com/&quot;&gt;Fight Health Insurance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Have you ever been denied a health insurance claim? This site was built by a user who was sick and tired and wanted to help others. So this was created using an LLM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sfstandard.com/2024/08/23/holden-karau-fight-health-insurance-appeal-claims-denials/&quot;&gt;&#39;Make your health insurance company cry&#39;: One woman’s fight to turn the tables on insurers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
An article on the previous link.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://landsat.gsfc.nasa.gov/apps/YourNameInLandsat-main/index.html&quot;&gt;Your name in LANDSAT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This is just cool. 😎&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 35/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Oceans of tiredness</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/oceans-of-tiredness/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-25T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/oceans-of-tiredness/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Just got back from taking the kiddos to the local water and amusement park locale...we are all incredibly tired and wore out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was, supposedly, a heat warning kinda day - but honestly it didn&#39;t seem nearly as bad as it has in the past. At the park, I didn&#39;t even get in too bad a shape until towards the end, and to be realistic I was actually cold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It goes along with water and not having a large amount of body fat these days. Something of a side effect I suppose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After spending some time with the kiddos in the wave pool, we headed over to the adjoining amusement park and fed the family. The nearby diner has a decent selection of, well, cheeseburgers or chicken fingers, salad, fruit, fries and onion rings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lots of stuff that the kids like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since we have four &amp;quot;dining meals&amp;quot; to go along with the gold entry passes, it makes things more worth it to eat a couple of meals there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, good grief am I shockingly sore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;link-dump&quot;&gt;Link dump &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#link-dump&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t know how much I&#39;ll have for the weekly link dumpage, but here we go!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mayank99/11ty-jsx-deno&quot;&gt;mayank99 11ty jsx and tsx template&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I&#39;m not really a huge fan of jsx style templating, but I can certainly appreciate the work that others have put in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.evalapply.org/posts/clojure-web-app-from-scratch/index.html&quot;&gt;Aditya Athalye - Clojuring the web application stack: Meditation One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I haven&#39;t read all of this one, but I&#39;m looking forward to going through it all. I love clojure, and I like trying to write apps and web apps with it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.analog.cafe/r/a-functional-lego-camera-kit-lego-zh1-i9j8&quot;&gt;Zung Hoang - LEGO camera that works!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
As an &lt;em&gt;adult fan of LEGO&lt;/em&gt;, I love this &lt;strong&gt;a lot&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All right, I&#39;m gonna call that a night!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take care, till next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 32/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Notes of yesterday</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/notes-of-yesterday/"/>
		<updated>2024-06-09T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/notes-of-yesterday/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;I did not post anything yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After over a month of managing to get something put up, I skipped a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And you know what? That&#39;s okay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s not a habit until it becomes something more normal. I hope that days like yesterday are more the exception than the rule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was some productivity that was had yesterday, despite the overnight rain I was able to get the lawn mowed and some other weeds taken care of. We&#39;ve got an older Snapper battery operated lawnmower, and I consider it a major accomplishment if I&#39;m able to get the lawn mowed within a single 4Ah battery. If I can get it weekly, it&#39;s usually possible, and only takes about an hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, I really need to run the weed eater though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second vehicle is still at the dealership, hopefully it&#39;s finished by Monday afternoon. It really stinks not having my car. Not that I go anywhere, or that I could go anywhere at this time. But still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve got a question into our insurance agent, wondering about a few things that are related about that vehicle issue, but I&#39;m not overly optimistic about any responses there. Certainly nothing favorable, anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s getting close to that time to begin thinking about birthday gifts for the spouse. Sometimes I&#39;m just not really in a gift giving mood, and this seems to be one of those times. I do, however, think I know what I&#39;m going to get, so that&#39;s positive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;last-week&#39;s-links&quot;&gt;Last Week&#39;s Links &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#last-week&#39;s-links&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I&#39;m going to start something new here, too, this week. In something of an effort to reduce the number of open tabs that I have on my phone, I&#39;m going to add to a listing of links that I&#39;ve found of interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://tiddlywiki.com/&quot;&gt;TiddlyWiki&lt;/a&gt; an older single file wiki based, server less, personal knowledge base application. I haven&#39;t used this in forever, it&#39;s good to see it&#39;s still kicking though.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linode.com/docs/guides/how-to-install-and-configure-hubzilla/&quot;&gt;How to install and configure hubzilla&lt;/a&gt; I like the idea of Hubzilla, and I also like the idea of running my own fediverse something or other. I already have plenty of them, though, and don&#39;t need to &lt;em&gt;collect them all&lt;/em&gt; in this case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.itsfoss.com/ente-auth/&quot;&gt;Ente Auth&lt;/a&gt; I really need to get away from Google Authenticator, since it kinda stinks. You&#39;d think that Google would at least provide some kind of &lt;em&gt;search&lt;/em&gt; for theirs, but.... That&#39;s asking quite a lot. Ente seems pretty cool, they&#39;ve also got a photos replacement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cara.app/home&quot;&gt;Cara&lt;/a&gt; Something of an Instagram replacement that has had really good growth over the last few weeks from what I see. They have really strong safeguards and stances on AI.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
