<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>My Corner of the Internet Feed for orgmode</title>
	<subtitle>Just my little corner of the internet.</subtitle>
	
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/"/>
	<updated>2024-10-19T15:51:44+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://shanewrogers.lol</id>
	<author>
		<name>Shane Rogers</name>
		<email>swrogers@omg.lol</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Trying to leave OneNote</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/trying-to-leave-onenote/"/>
		<updated>2024-10-10T15:21:38+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/trying-to-leave-onenote/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;This particular post is most likely just going to be of interest to future me, though some others may find some information of use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As my place of employment is a Microsoft shop, we use a large number of Microsoft applications. Personally, I&#39;m not really a major fan of some of these apps so I like to look for good alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, I have grown used to being in the WSL environment and Emacs in particular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Historically I have been using OneNote to keep track of, um, notes and tidbits and whatever else one might want to put into a notebook. It has worked &lt;em&gt;just fine&lt;/em&gt; but I don&#39;t like the fact that I don&#39;t have a lot of control over the format. I&#39;ve kind of grown fond of just using text, and have been attempting to integrate Emacs&#39; org-mode into more of my workflow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(I would love to say that I&#39;m using org-mode for this blog, but alas, I am not - although it &lt;strong&gt;is&lt;/strong&gt; plain markdown.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently came upon a tool that caught my interest, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alopezrivera/OneNoteExporter&quot; title=&quot;OneNoteExporter by alopezrivera&quot;&gt;OneNoteExporter&lt;/a&gt; PowerShell script from &lt;strong&gt;alopezrivera&lt;/strong&gt;. Easily enough installed into my Windows 11 laptop, it only really required pandoc as an additional requirement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once I had the configuration file tweaked to my liking, I fired the script off. Of note, the powershell script needs to run at the same user level elevation as the currently running OneNote application. Also, a temporary script bypass may need to be run in powershell in order for the process to succeed: &lt;code&gt;Set-ExecutionPolicy ByPass -Scope Process&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a handful of errors at first, which were similar &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alopezrivera/OneNoteExporter/issues/11&quot;&gt;to this issue&lt;/a&gt;. I was able to make the same edit as suggested and those problems were resolved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next stumbling block that I came upon was the large amount of screenshots and images that I had in my OneNote notebooks. Those were not being exported by the pandoc process. As is normal within the world of the internet, I &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/theohbrothers/ConvertOneNote2MarkDown/issues/183&quot;&gt;was not the first person to have this problem&lt;/a&gt;. One thing that I most absolutely &lt;em&gt;did not&lt;/em&gt; want to have to do was re-save all of those images in another format, &lt;strong&gt;or&lt;/strong&gt; copy and paste the pages themselves into a new page - both of which were suggested as possible solutions. Thankfully, a very simple solution was found by another user &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/theohbrothers/ConvertOneNote2MarkDown/issues/183#issuecomment-2343708831&quot;&gt;in that OneNote needs to download all files and images before syncing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that issue taken care of, everything was golden, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mostly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still had to go through and add the proper filename extension to all of my fresh org files. Still haven&#39;t figured out why that was, but it was easy enough with emacs and wdired mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, with my work related notes over in org mode and copied up to the work OneDrive I should be ready to roll.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is post 45/100 of my #100DaysToOffload posts. You can read the other posts in this series &lt;a href=&quot;https://shanewrogers.lol/tags/100daystooffload&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
