<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>My Corner of the Internet Feed for todo</title>
	<subtitle>Just my little corner of the internet.</subtitle>
	
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/"/>
	<updated>2024-09-24T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://shanewrogers.lol</id>
	<author>
		<name>Shane Rogers</name>
		<email>swrogers@omg.lol</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Now that we have reloaded</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/now-that-we-have-reloaded/"/>
		<updated>2024-03-18T18:05:18+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/now-that-we-have-reloaded/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h1 id=&quot;capture-template---sorta-done&quot;&gt;Capture template - Sorta Done &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#capture-template---sorta-done&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, it&#39;s done enough that I think I&#39;m gonna call it &lt;em&gt;good enough&lt;/em&gt; at this point. I&#39;m not particularly happy with the yasnippet yet, in that I can&#39;ts eem to get the &lt;code&gt;tags&lt;/code&gt; entry items to space over and have to do that manually. Whatever. It&#39;s fine. It&#39;s all good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I need to add a setting into the org capture portion to make sure that the capture window takes up the whole frame, or at least isn&#39;t mirrored in another portion of my frame. It&#39;s all good, though. That must be the Pete the Cat in me talking. Ha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also had to suppress the emacs warning from yasnippet that complained about changing the buffer - so I may have to either live with what I&#39;ll consider a hack, or come up with a better way to insert the ISO creation time stamp for the date frontmatter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m sure there is more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still plenty of stuff to work on: setting up some data store files to pull in my other feeds, checking into basic webmentions (because I&#39;m super, uber popular....ha)....among other items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This slug is acting funny.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Capture Template Done?</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/capture-template-done/"/>
		<updated>2024-03-18T17:35:37+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/capture-template-done/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;h1 id=&quot;step-two%2C-maybe&quot;&gt;Step Two, Maybe &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#step-two%2C-maybe&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capture template might be ready to go, now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Created a new markdown post in the proper directory, with a prompt for the file name, then prepends the year-mm-dd to the file name. Opens a nice empty file, ready for the yasnippet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could probably put more into the capture template to do away with the snippet.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
