<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>My Corner of the Internet Feed for workspace</title>
	<subtitle>Just my little corner of the internet.</subtitle>
	
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/"/>
	<updated>2024-12-31T13:05:11+00:00</updated>
	<id>https://shanewrogers.lol</id>
	<author>
		<name>Shane Rogers</name>
		<email>swrogers@omg.lol</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Not a tall tale</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-a-tall-tale/"/>
		<updated>2024-06-13T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/not-a-tall-tale/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Ah, the &lt;em&gt;Tale of the Telluride&lt;/em&gt; just will not quit. It&#39;s like the gift that keeps on giving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But then, how often are things &amp;quot;good&amp;quot; when &lt;strong&gt;that&lt;/strong&gt; particular phrase comes into play. Yeah, not all that often.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So after paying too stonking much for repairs due to a, um, we shall say &amp;quot;self imposed&amp;quot; accident, now it looks like we might have a little bit of salt rubbed into that festering wound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know, for good measure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it&#39;s probably entirely coincidental, it looks like we&#39;ll be replacing the battery in the beast. Twice today when going to start it up we&#39;ve experienced a series of error checks (ECS, BCW, blah blah blah) and clicks and basically what looks like a computer system spasming out and proverbially vomiting all over itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s great. The vehicle is a 2021, so I guess it&#39;s about that time for the OEM battery to go. At least that&#39;s the opinion of the interwebs, that they&#39;ll last about 2.5 years. I don&#39;t mind, really. Having the battery die or running out of gas are about two of the larger vehicle fears that I have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully that&#39;s what the problem is.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The mobile posting process</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-mobile-posting-process/"/>
		<updated>2024-06-05T15:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-mobile-posting-process/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;All of the following is more for myself and future reference than anything. (Though, who am I kidding, this whole blog thing is all personal future reference, isn&#39;t it?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I figure that I&#39;ve been blogging this way for a month or better at this point, so it might be worthwhile to get down what my current process is for getting a post up. I&#39;ll even include some nifty screenshots. All from mobile, even!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-process&quot;&gt;The process &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#the-process&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently my site is statically generated by way of eleventy, hosted on GitHub pages, using porkbun as DNS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My writing is done using Zettel Notes on Android, using Markdown and it connects to my GitHub repository to push and pull as needed. The push triggers a GitHub action to update the static pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-flow&quot;&gt;The flow &lt;a class=&quot;direct-link&quot; href=&quot;#the-flow&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is where I start things off, using Zettel Notes I open my &amp;quot;local&amp;quot; storage on my phone via the App Directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.some.pics/swrogers/666086db7dca8.png&quot; alt=&quot;Zettel Notes screenshot on Android. Shows a portion of the side menu.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve got a handful of templates and half started junk in here - I really should clean this out. The main item of interest is the &lt;code&gt;blog-template-default.md&lt;/code&gt; file here, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I open that file up and copy the contents...&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.some.pics/swrogers/6660872d78e5f.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the Zettel Notes app on Android. Shows the main &amp;quot;App Folder&amp;quot; directory listing where I keep my blog drafts and templates.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...into a new entry within the Blog drafts directory. Ive got Zettel set up to automatically name the new note entries with the date as I like, I just have to add the rest of the file name and the extension.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To the rest of the yaml front matter I will add the title, change the date (the only thing I have yet to figure out if is easily automated in Zettel or not) and the tags.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.some.pics/swrogers/6660878ee41f6.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the Zettel Notes application on Android. Shows the text of the yaml front matter that I use for my default blog posts.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After I edit the file, I then manually copy the note into the posts directory of the Lol Blog section/repository and refresh the listing. This initiates the needed push to start the publishing process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any images that I use, I have just been uploading to my omg.lol pictures area and copying the markdown links. It works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s all kind of clunky, manual, somewhat kludgy, but it works for me.&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The Steam Deck Age</title>
		<link href="https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-steam-deck-age/"/>
		<updated>2024-06-01T21:05:11+00:00</updated>
		<id>https://shanewrogers.lol/posts/the-steam-deck-age/</id>
		<content type="html">
		  &lt;p&gt;Just because the May challenge is over doesn&#39;t mean that I can&#39;t still try to keep some writing going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I had stated earlier, I&#39;ve had the opportunity to move my workspace into a downstairs location, and I think I kind of like how things are situated now. It&#39;s a good feeling to have a nice clean start, without quite so much clutter. I had even brought another box down, but said to myself: &amp;quot;Self, do I really need to bring all this crap down here? No. No I do not.&amp;quot; At which point, I promptly packed that box back and trotted it right back upstairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably one of the nicest bonuses to having this setup down here is that I can dock my SteamDeck and play it without feeling too guilty about not being around the family. I don&#39;t get a whole lot of time to game these days, so I haven&#39;t really been able to take advantage of having my Deck. Now, maybe that can change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.some.pics/swrogers/665b8cc3b09c1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cropped image of my work area, with the Steamdeck docked.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All right, with that I think it&#39;s getting to be about time to get some dinner prepped. It&#39;s spaghetti squash with homemade alfredo night, with a side of asparagus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a good night all!&lt;/p&gt;

			
		</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
